al
al
[Music]
[Música]
e
e
H
H
[Music]
[Música]
B
B
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
H
H
and
y
[Music] [
[Música]
H [Music] [
H
Applause]
[Música]
H [Music] Oh [Music]
H
and [Music] ah [Music] H [Music]
y
ah [Music] H [
ah
Music] [Applause]
[Música]
the [Music]
el
H
H
[Music]
[Música]
B
B
he
he
[Music] [Music]
[Música]
you
ti
Good evening my people how are you?
buenísimas noches mi gente qué tal
Look at the audio I can't watch an
estáis Mira el audio no puedo mirar un
audio right now the truth is I have my
audio ahora mismo la verdad es que tengo
eyes very
los ojos muy
busy What's up What's up
ocupados Qué
But Javi helps to build
pasa Qué pasa Pero Javi ayuda a forjar
character do you want me to do a little bit I'll
carácter queréis que os haga un poquito
do a little bit of bullying that according to
os hag un poquito de bullying que según
these three Hey let's leave the subject I have
estos tres Oye vamos a dejar el tema ya
not squeezed the subject to the maximum I can't,
no he exprimido el tema a más no poder
the subject has made the weekend for me in
me ha hecho fin de semana el tema de
fact let's see how it went I just
hecho a ver que yo vea cómo ha
came from watching your video it has been a very
ido vengo de ver tu videoo de ha muy
good trip Although the whole subject It left me with a
buen vío Aunque todo el tema Me dejó con
very bad feeling thanks I hope everything gets better
muy mal cuerpo gracias Ojalá todo mejore
soon over there Greetings Javi and chat Thank you very
pronto por allá Saludos Javi y chat
much man Thank you very much
Muchas gracias tío Muchas gracias Me
Can you send me another
podéis mandar otro
fit can you send another one please because it's
fit podis mandar otro por favor porque
driving me crazy that it appears
es que me tiene loco eso de que aparece
double it appears double the la la alert and
doble aparece doble la la la alerta y
that I don't know where it appears double it
que no Pillo de dónde aparece doble me
has me completely
tiene loquísimo
lost let's see let's say it was this let
perdido a ver digamos que era este
me know if it appears double okay again
avisarme si aparece doble vale otra vez
Tito let's see how the subject went first first
Tito a ver ha ido el tema primer primer
review No look now Gabrielo does not
repasito No mira ahora gabrielo no
appear double but it is sometimes I don't know
aparece doble pero es a veces no sé por
why sometimes when the  members do not
qué a veces cuando los miembros no
appear double the Twitch bits appear double
aparece doble aparece doble los bit de
and I want to know why it is that I do
Twitch y quiero saber el porqué es que
not know why but the other day
no sé el porqué pero es que el otro día
in the debate was happening well let's see Javi the
en el debate pasaba bueno a ver Javi el
little one Javier the little one Javier little one I have
canijo Javier el canijo Javier canijo el
exploited the subject but we are going
tema lo he explotado pero vamos de
crazy Javier little one is going to be 6
manera loca Javier canijo va a ser 6
million visits this month Javier
millones de visitas este mes Javier
little one I think that this month it is the channel we will
canijo creo que este mes es el canal ya
see it in the lists at the end of the month
lo veremos en las listas final de mes
but I think it is the gossip channel the most
pero creo que es el canal de salseo má
viewed gossip channel this
viton el canal de cotillo má visto este
month one more month okay And there is still
mes un mes más vale Y todavía queda
half a month left we can still demonstrate
medio mes todavía podemos demostrar
our worth much more let's
mucho más nuestra valía vamos a
update the bar not before doing
actualizar la barra no antes de haceros
The spam let's update the
El spam vamos a actualizar la barra de
members bar someone wants to know how many
miembros alguien quiere saber cuántos
members we are well we are
miembros
2000 Uy 2000
somos pues somos 2000 Uy 2000
3256 we must update the bar
3256 hay que actualizar la barra
3256 javiel little one does not exist churra if
3256 javiel canijo no existe churra si
you search for javiel little one
tú buscas por javiel canijo te aparece
this channel appears I left the ara the ara of this
este canal dejé el ara el ara de este
channel the URL the link is javel little one I
canal el URL el enlace Es javel canijo
left it as a
lo dejé como
tribute I left it as a tribute to see member
homenaje lo dejé como homenaje a ver
member
member member
goal member goal let's see members the
goal member goal vamos a ver miembros la
salsería target amount
salsería cantidad objetivo
4000 we said
4000 hemos dicho
3256 self-criticism a
3256 autocrítica un
kiss let's see there's the bar already
beso a ver ahí está la barra ya
updated my goodness
actualizada madre mía
3256 yes I had like a little bit of a spill
3256 sí tenía como un poco de derrame
Javi and the eye how are you
Javi y el ojo qué tal
Rosa it's been two months since that my weapon
Rosa hace ya dos meses de eso mi arma
you're a little lost eh Rosa thank goodness Thank goodness you've been to
estás un poco perdida eh Rosa menos mal
me every day
Menos mal que me habéis todos los días
Eh gentlemen we have to get our act together
Eh señoreros tenemos que poner las pilas
with this member situation that's
con esta situación de miembro eso es
your problem this that's your
vuestro problema esto eso es vuestro
problem let's see here guys here
problema a ver aquí chavales aquí
guys apart from the members I'm going to
chavales aparte de los miembros voy a
remember two
recordar dos
things before starting with the subject
cosas antes de empezar con el tema
okay two things only okay two things
vale dos cosas solamente vale dos cosas
only the video has just been uploaded the
solamente se acaba de subir vídeo
video has just been uploaded on the
se acaba de subir vídeo en el canal
main channel okay a little while before
principal vale un ratito antes
just uh starting the live
justamente de eh de empezar el directo
Okay now before starting the live
Vale ahora antes de empezar el directo
what I've done is record
lo que he hecho ha sido grabar el de
tomorrow's because as I already told you okay as I
mañana porque como ya os dije vale como
already told you We're going to try to give
ya os dije Vamos a intentar darle un
the Main Channel a little bit of support
poquito de cañita al Canal principal
this means that the main channel is
esto quiere decir que el canal principal
only going to deal with topics like this seriously
solamente va a tratar de temas así serio
no this this means that the
no esto esto quiere decir que el canal
main channel is going to be like  formerly I'm
principal va a ser como antiguamente me
going to see goodbye don't go Gustavo don't
voy a ver adiós no te vayas Gustavo no
go see it later when we finish
te vayas lo ves luego cuando terminemos
the live I'll remember it again and we'll
el directo lo volveré a recordar y lo
see it when you see it When I
vemos cuando lo veis ustedes Cuando
finish the live okay you see it
termine el directo vale ustedes lo veis
when I finish the live now you
cuando termine el directo ahora os
stay here becoming a member okay
quedáis aquí haciéndose miembro vale
good video Javi studying a little
buen vídeo Javi estudiando un poco de
history now Okay it's a serious video it
historia ahora Bueno es un vídeo serio
's a serious video eh we're going to try to make
es un vídeo serio eh vamos a intentar
the main channel
que el canal principal
have a certain quality okay we're going to
tenga cierta calidad vale vamos a
try to recover the rhythm and
intentar volver a recuperar el ritmo y
the direction of the main Channel that doesn't
el rumbo del Canal principal eso no
mean that we are exempt from
quiere decir que que estemos exentos de
having gossip from
que haya salseo de
youtubers okay em on
youtubers vale
the main channel okay it doesn't
em en el canal principal vale no quiere
mean that there is no youtuber that there won't be
decir que no haya youtuber que no vaya a
gossip from youtubers on the
ver salseo de youtubers en el canal
main channel when it's a video like
principal cuando sea un vídeo como
some of the ones we've done in the
alguno de los que hemos hecho en la
salsería I've already said it
salsería ya lo he dicho
okay In fact I regret having
vale De hecho me arrepiento de haberlo
uploaded it to the salsería and not here okay
subido a la salsería y no aquí vale
let's let's let's give back the
vamos a vamos a volver a darle el
meaning to the main Channel that it had
sentido al Canal principal que tenía
okay let's give back the meaning and let's
vale vamos a volver a darle el sentido y
see what happens videos that are going to be uploaded
a ver qué pasa vídeos que se van a subir
on the main channel well videos
en el canal principal pues vídeos
like
como
this Okay this depends okay This is a
este Bueno este depende vale Este es un
little good come on yeah like this Yeah
poco bueno venga sí como este Sí
surely Yeah this one for example wasn't it wasn't that big of a
seguramente Sí este por ejemplo no fue
deal This one with Jimbo and
no fue para tanto Este lo de jimbo y
all that wasn't that big of a deal we'll
demás no fue para tanto eso lo vamos a
decide that when they're edited okay the
decidir cuando estén editados vale el
editor and I will decide which ones
editor y yo los vamos a decidir los que
go on the main page or which ones aren't worth it
van para el principal o los que no vale
but man I think that obviously
pero hombre Yo creo que evidentemente
videos like this guy Look at this How good
vídeos como este tío Mira este Qué bueno
was this video, how good it was This
fue este vídeo que bien estaba Este
video dude we uploaded it there on the salsería
vídeo tío lo subimos ahí en la salsería
because it was from a youtuber this one also from
porque era de youtuber este también de
Huesca, it was very good okay I think you
huesco le estuvo muy bien vale creo que
understand me right What kind of videos go
me entendéis no Qué tipo de vídeos van
there on the
ahí en el
main page instead of on the salsería or on
principal en vez de la salsería o en
telesalseo okay this guy Ah this one I
telesalseo vale este tío Ah este me
regret that it's here on the
arrepiento de que esté aquí en la
salsería dude I'm not going to reupload it
salsería tío ya no lo voy a resubir
obviously but this one okay
evidentemente pero este vale vídeos de
telesalseo videos too eh
telesalseo también eh vídeos de
telesalseo videos Like for example
telesalseo Como por ejemplo el
Chanel's this guy this video was very
Chanel este tío este vídeo estuvo muy
good the other
bueno el otro
day this video the other day was very
día este vídeo el otro día estuvo muy
good okay we uploaded it there to telesalseo
bueno vale lo subimos ahí a telesalseo
because it was from there
porque era de ahí
eh But well from now on these
eh Pero bueno a partir de ahora esto
these types of videos will go  in the main one
este tipo de vídeos Irán en el principal
okay eh And the one of Queen Letizia
vale eh Y el de la reina Leticia
man this guy who already has almost 100,000
tío este tío que tiene ya casi 100000
views man tomorrow the one that goes up is a
visitas tío mañana el que se sube es un
style like this eh Well yes it could be a
estilo a este eh Bueno sí podría ser un
style like this but maybe not so much
estilo a es pero a lo mejor no tanto
about K midelton tomorrow
sobre K midelton el de mañana el de
tomorrow a kiss a kiss But well okay there will
mañana un beso un beso Pero bueno vale
be a bit of
habrá un poco de
everything on the main channel okay there will be a
todo en el canal principal vale habrá un
bit of everything okay There you have it I have
poco de todo vale Ahí lo tenéis he
changed the photo of the Main Channel it has not been
cambiado la foto del Canal principal no
updated well I have still put
se ha actualizado bien Todavía he puesto
that one I don't know if you like it but I was not
esa no sé si os gusta pero no me
convinced by the one that was
terminaba de convencer la que estaba
posted I am not a restless ass I do not leave
puesta no soy un culo inquieto no dejo
anything still eh I do not leave anything still eh I do not
quieto nada eh No dejo quieto nada eh No
leave anything still eh But well I have
dejo quieto nada eh Pero bueno lo he
said it okay I will remember it when
dicho vale lo recordaré cuando
we finish the live go support the
terminemos el directo iros a a apoyar el
video that I have uploaded okay the truth
vídeo que he subido vale que la verdad
is that it has a lot of work in another
es que tiene bastante curro en otro
order of things okay finishing with the
orden de cosas vale terminando con los
ads eh or continuing with the
anuncios eh o continuando con los
ads they have closed the
anuncios han vuelto a cerrar la la
[ __ ] tiktok account again man they
puñetera cuenta de de tiktok tío no lo
have not closed it again the [ __ ]
han vuelto a cerrar la puñetera cuenta
tiktok account they have closed it for us  closed again eh I
de tiktok nos lo han vuelto a cerrar eh
imagine it will be any bunch of
me imagino que será cualquier panda de
[ __ ] stalkers worth all
acosadores de [__] [__] vale todo el
day reporting and tiktok working like
día reportando y tiktok funcionando como
[ __ ] Okay so what am I going
el culo Vale entonces qué es lo que voy
to do the next time we
a hacer la próxima vez que la
get it back the next time we
recuperemos la próxima vez que la
get it back I'm going to try to talk to
recuperemos voy a intentar hablar con
tiktok by all means so that they
tiktok por todos los medios para que me
verify it for me man I mean, put a
la verifiquen tío O sea que le pongan un
verification I don't know if with the verification they will
verificado no sé si con el verificado se
have a little more care eh when it is
tendrá un poquito más de cuidado eh a la
thrown with so much Oh
a hora de de que se tire con tanta Ay
sun solstice Thank you very much
sol solsticio Muchísimas gracias
welcome Thank you very much for becoming a
bienvenida Muchas gracias por hacerte
member I don't know if when I don't know if when they
miembro no sé si cuando no sé si cuando
verify the accounts I don't know if being
verifican las cuentas no sé si estando
verified you have a little more
verificadas se tiene un poquito más de
endurance so that they don't throw it away so much but oh
aguante para que no la tiren tanto pero
well please this is very important
bueno por favor esto es muy importante
okay you're going to help me
vale me me vais a ayudar
everyone you're going to help me everyone okay so I mean this
todos me vais a ayudar todos vale o sea
way this way we get it back the
forma de esta forma la recuperamos la
next time in one
otra vez en un
day While I was in Thailand don't
día Estando yo en Tailandia no te lo
miss it eh I put it and asked for it in the
pierdas eh lo puse y lo pedí en el grupo
WhatsApp group I put it and asked for it in the
de WhatsApp lo puse y lo pedí en el
WhatsApp group people  collaborated okay you
grupo de WhatsApp la gente colaboró vale
all collaborated Well I don't know if all
colaboraste todos Bueno no sé si todos
but many for sure and they gave me back
pero muchos seguro y me y me devolvieron
the account
la cuenta
dude and they gave me back the account are you going to
tío y me devolvieron la cuenta vas a
talk about the bef between nixter and se Well I don't
hablar del bef entre nixter y se Pues no
know who sein is honestly but
sé quién es sein la verdad pero me
you told me the other day that not even saxer
dijisteis el otro día que ni saxer me
hit on me bf which I doubt because the truth is I
tiró bf que lo dudo porque la verdad me
get along well with her but well maybe she
llevo bien con ella pero bueno a lo
hit on me a little bifit but
mejor me ha tirado un poco de bifit pero
you told me in the chat but you didn't
me lo dijisteis en el chat pero no me lo
send it to me in the end I have three or
no me lo mandaste al final tengo tres o
four songs prepared I'm going to go all out I do
cuatro temas preparados voy a ir a saco
n't want the live show to last 3 hours
no quiero que el directo dure 3 horas
because I signed up for
porque me he apuntado a
crossfit Monday and Wednesday morning
crossfit lunes y miércoles por la mañana
grofit and full body
grofit y full body
Monday and Wednesday
lunes y miércoles por la
night were the dates I had free I know
noche eran las citas que había libre sé
that s are both on the same day
que s son las dos cosas del mismo día
but oh well I imagine that Monday and
pero bueno Me imagino que lunes y
Wednesday will be a bit [ __ ] but oh
miércoles estaré un poco a [__] pero
well I'm going to that's life That's
bueno voy a esa es la vida Esa es la
life I'm going to give it a chance I'm going all
vida le voy a dado una oportunidad voy a
out eh I'm going all out Eh You're going to last TR
saco eh voy a saco Eh Vas a durar TR
days in the coffit no no no no I'm not going all out
días en el coffit no no no no voy a saco
eh this this summer I'm going to be another I'm
eh este este verano voy a ser otro ya os
telling you this summer I'm going to be another this this
lo digo este verano voy a ser otro este
time yes eh This time yes This time yes eh This
eh Esta vez sí Esta vez sí
time yes eh this time I'm going for it
eh Esta vez sí eh esta vez voy a saco
eh
eh
says eito can you imagine that the T only under
dice eito te imaginas que el T solo bajo
glass mly would literally fulfill his
cristal mly literalmente cumpliría su
pseudo threat let's see what I tell you I mean it could
pseudo amenaza a ver que te digo o sea
be glass Molly as it could be
podría ser cristal Molly como podría ser
anyone that for
cualquiera que por
enemies Bob Thank you very much A kiss
enemigos Bob Muchas gracias Un beso
friend Bob 96 let's see we estimate in
amigo Bob 96 a ver estimamos en
enemies let's go in enemy I'm
enemigos vamos en enemigo ya te lo
telling you important statement from Javi
digo comunicado importante de Javi
Oliveira about his tiktok account well
oliveira sobre su cuenta de tiktok bueno
these are the steps to follow okay for them to
estos son los pasos a seguir vale para
give it back to me But you have to
que me la devuelvan Pero esto lo tenéis
do this please you
que hacer ustedes por favor ustedes
The more the
Cuantos más
better The more the better okay in 24
mejor Cuantos más mejor vale en en 24
hours the other time he answered me on tiktok
horas la otra vez me contestó tiktok lo
I asked for it in the WhatsApp group I don't have
pedí en el grupo de WhatsApp no tengo
tiktok believe it no Let's see don't start
tiktok te lo creas no A ver no empecéis
telling me your problems that I don't
a contarme vuestros problemas que no me
care about okay what matters here are
importan vale lo que importa aquí son
mine I'm going King okay one from your
los míos voy Rey vale uno desde vuestro
profile you give the three lines that
perfil le dais a las tres rayitas que
are these not the ones you get in the 3
son estas no las que os metéis a las 3
of the  Okay let's see
de la Bueno vamos a ver
man, okay, you hit the three
tío esta vale le dais a las tres
lines, settings, and
rayitas ajustes y
privacy, Javi already said it. I haven't
privacidad ya lo dice Javi No lo he
explained it bl, I haven't explained it, I'm
explicado bl no lo he explicado lo estoy
explaining it now again, okay, you do it
explicando ahora otra vez vale lo
again, and
volvéis a hacer y
privacy,
privacidad
okay, report a
vale informar de un
problem, laziness, no secret, you
problema pereza no secre lo
do it Javi, I don't understand tiktok,
haces Javi yo no lo entiendo a tiktok
man, don't tell me your [ __ ]
tío que no me contéis vuestros [__]
problems, really, I'm
problemas de verdad es que os estoy
telling you something important that you have to do
diciendo algo importante que tenéis que
and you're telling me your
hacer y me estáis contando vuestros
[ __ ] problems Jai, my
[__] problemas Jai se me han quedado
shoes have become too small for me, oyo, do you want to go a
chicos los zapatos oyo queréis ir un
little crazy and do this that I
poco a la [__] y hacer esto que os
'm
estoy
asking you to go through Javi? Suck my dick,
pidiendo pasando Javi Chúpame la [__]
lord, do it right now, man? You have
lord lo haces ahora mismo tío Tienes
something more important to
otra cosa más importante que
do, you do it and that's it, man, let's
hacer lo haces y punto tío vamos a
start again that you've
empezar otra vez que me habéis
confused me, your profile, the three lines,
liado a vuestro perfil las tres rayitas
keep quiet, the three
calladito las tres
lines, settings, and
rayitas ajustes y
privacy, report a
privacidad informar de un
problem, send a
problema enviar
report, okay, Pablo Franco, send the
denuncia vale Pablo Franco envía las
reports since you have to send, send a
denuncias ya que tienes que enviar
report and there you
denuncia y ahí
write and there you write, the account
escribís y ahí escribís la la cuenta
called @j oliveira 5 has been banned
llamada @j oliveira 5 ha sido baneada
by mistake he's my idol he's the best
por error es mi ídolo es el mejor
creator of please send me that okay
creador de por favor mandarme eso vale
send me a screenshot of that when you do it
mandarme captura de eso cuando la hagáis
okay put me on Twitter screenshots of that
vale ponerme en Twitter capturas de eso
when you do it please tiktok is not the
cuando lo hagáis por favor tiktok no es
same without @javioliveira I beg you
lo mismo sin @ javioliveira
restore it as soon as possible and
ruego la restauren cuanto antes y
send a photo a screenshot if you
mandáis una foto una captura si la
have it okay you can get it by
tenéis vale que la podéis conseguir
searching on Google search for @javioliveira
buscando en Google buscáis @
tiktok and search for it it's not the same tiktok
tiktok y la busc no es lo mismo tiktok
I'm going to uninstall tiktok if it doesn't come back @javioliveira
me voy a desinstalar tiktok si no vuelve
5 please okay I mean
@ javioliveira 5 por favor vale o sea
that kind of things my grandmother
ese tipo de cosas mi abuela bailaba
always danced to the rhythm of Javi oliveira 5
siempre al ritmo de Javi oliveira 5
things
cosas
like that okay
así
okay the account called @abi
vale vale la cuenta llamada @abi
oliveira has been banned by
oliveira ha sido baneada por
mistake and Dallas is worse And don't
error y Dallas es peor Y no lo
ban it okay things like that restore it as soon as
bane vale cosas así la restauren cuanto
possible no but to ask them please
antes no pero pedírselo por favor por
please they closed it by mistake I beg you
favor la han cerrado por error ruego la
restore it as soon as possible
restauren cuanto antes
okay I beg you will restore it as soon as possible
vale ruego la restauro en cuanto antes
okay and you hit send that's it dude you don't
vale y le dais a enviar ya está tío no
have to do anything else
tenéis que hacer más nada
okay its too much to ask that you all do that
vale es mucho pedir que hagáis eso todos
please  And what do you give us in return, well,
por favor Y qué nos das a cambio pues
content on tiktok, having an account,
contenido en tiktok teniendo cuenta
content on tiktok,
contenido en tiktok
of course, content on
claro contenido en
tiktok, wow, wow, wow, leak, wow, leak, I just did it, let's see, I'm going to
tiktok
try to
voy a intentar
solve it, I'm going to try, I'm going to
solucionarlo voy a
try to solve it, I don't
intentar voy a intentar solucionarlo no
know if I'm going to be very on time, I'm also
sé si voy a estar muy a tiempo también
telling you, it's not that I worry too much, in
te digo no es que me preocupe mucho de
fact, in fact, I would even say that I don't
hecho de hecho yo diría incluso que me
give a damn
suda un poco los
the truth is it's not my problem, it's not my
[__] la verdad no es mi problema no
fault, no liad issimo, no
culpa no liad issimo no
ladsim, no, I don't know, well maybe yes, eh, wow,
ladsim no no sé bueno a lo mejor sí eh
Li, wow, le, wow, tomorrow's
buah vaya Li vaya le vaya le mañana
video, did you see Agustín's, no, what,
videazo viste lo de Agustín no el qué
what, what a lick? No, seriously, I'm sucking on the dick, see? It
qué vaya lick No en serio me su la [__]
's not my problem, it's not mine, eh. It's not
ver No es mi problema no es mío eh No es
mine, the message, let's see,
mío el mensaje a ver
ta. Oh, I
ta
closed the vertical,
Ay cerré el vertical
wait for it,
espérate
m if he closes the live vertical,
m si cierra el directo en vertical
revive YouTube. Yes, let's see, wait a
revive YouTube Sí a ver espera un
moment, I did a lick, let's see. I don't care, eh, I
momento hice un lck a ver Me da igual eh
mean, I directly don't give a
o sea directamente me la
damn, you did it directly, I don't give a
suda
damn. But
hecho directamente a mí me la suda Pero
well, I deleted it just in case, let's see
bueno lo he borrado por si acaso peramos
if it
que si se
leaks, I
filtra me trae sin
don't care.  it's me it's not me who looks
cuidado no es mi no soy yo el que queda
bad I
mal
was SAT But Javi oliveira 5 helped me
estaba SAT Pero Javi oliveira 5 me ayudó
well let's see then put
bueno a ver luego ponéis capturas de
screenshots okay then put screenshot
pantalla vale luego ponéis captura de
please when you've done it put
porfa cuando lo hayáis hecho ponéis
screenshot Okay when you've done it
pantalla Vale cuando lo hayáis hecho
put screenshots about what about what
ponerme capturas de pantalla sobre lo
happened already already Lu I have it I have it I have it I have it let's
ocurrido ya ya Lu lo tengo lo tengo lo
go the first thing we're going to see
tengo lo tengo lo tengo vamos lo primero
in
que vamos a ver de
fact come on okay very important too
hecho venga vale importantísimo también
eh Well let's see very important not
eh Bueno a ver importantísimo tampoco
that we waste our lives on
que se nos vaya la vida en
it Javi there are some Pelillos Rebelde that
ello Javi hay unos Pelillos Rebelde que
break the symmetry
rompen con la simetría
yes no no no it's all Flama it's all
sí no no no está tod Flama está tod
Flama Okay the last the last to
Flama Bueno lo último lo último para
start the live okay the last to
empezar el directo vale lo último para
start the live I would like I just
empezar el directo me gustaría acabo de
did an l I would like not to eat
hacer un l me gustaría no comerme la
Comanche's [ __ ] but I say it
Comanche pero lo digo de manera
literally I say it literally I would
literal lo digo de manera literal me
like not to eat Comanche's [ __ ]
gustaría no comerme la [__] de Comanche
Why Because in the thread there is a [ __ ]
Por qué Porque en el hilo hay una [__]
fast come on How many members would we have to
ráp vamos Cuántos miembros tendríamos
[ __ ] It's that I think it doesn't
que [__] Es que yo creo que no
exist I think it doesn't exist members
existe yo creo que no existe miembros
that I could ask to shave my head It's that I
que podría pedir para raparme Es que yo
think  it doesn't exist that the
creo que no existe que no existe la
possibility doesn't exist I think it wouldn't
posibilidad Yo creo que es que no
exist, let's say 100,000 members of course
existiría vamos 100000 miembros claro
100,000 members yes it's true if it exists, I mean, I have a
100000 miembros sí es verdad si existe o
price, eh, I have a price, man, I have a
sea tengo precio eh tengo precio tío
price, right, man, what a pain in the ass, he's
tengo precio verdad tío qué [__] soy
live and he says he has a
está en directo y dice que la tiene
little one Javi who wasn't the one,
pequeña Javi que no era la
well, let's see,
que bueno vamos a ver
let's see the funa and we'll see okay but
vamos a ver la funa y lo vemos vale pero
the last thing I want to ask you
lo último que os quiero pedir
moderators please pin
moderadores por favor fijar en el chat
the WhatsApp group in the chat, the link to the WhatsApp group
el grupo de WhatsApp el link del grupo
5000 members and it makes you Rasta,
WhatsApp 5000 miembros y te hace Rasta
not for 5000 members, not the
no por 5000 miembros no el grupo de
WhatsApp group, okay,
WhatsApp vale el grupo de WhatsApp porfa
the WhatsApp group, please, the WhatsApp group, please put it
el grupo de WhatsApp porfa ponedlo
pin it in the comments, put it
fijarlo en los comentarios ponerlo
pin it in the comments, okay, 3500
fijarlo en los comentarios vale 3500
people in the WhatsApp group I
personas en el grupo de WhatsApp Me
think it's very heavy what have they put Javi
parece muy heavy que qué han puesto Javi
This is not this is the screen that we
Esta no es esta es la pantalla que
should put okay let's see
tendríamos que poner vale a ver a partir
from this tweet now you think I'm pretty Okay
de este tweet ahora me crees linda Vale
now you think I'm pretty, it's
ahora me crees
better that you're 14 That's how you
linda mejor que tengas 14 Así vas
learn as a child Hehe
aprendiendo de pequeña Jeje
No no what the hell are we going to read
No no qué [__] es lo que vamos a leer
Okay From here I have to have
Bueno A partir de aquí tengo que tener
watch out because Comanche's penis is coming
cuidado porque viene el pene de Comanche
Okay what the [ __ ] I just read it I'm
Vale qué [__] Acabo de leer lo estoy
reading it here in small size okay please
leyendo aquí en pequeño vale por favor
remind me don't forget eh we have to
recordármelo no se nos olvide eh que
close the live and
tenemos que cerrar el directo y
delete it remind me please don't
eliminarlo recordármelo por favor no se
forget okay
nos olvide vale por
please when we get to that part
favor cuando lleguemos a esa parte por
please don't skip to the next tweet
favor que no pase al siguiente tweet
okay exposing Comanche for being a
vale exponiendo a Comanche por ser
groomer
groomer
okay 30000 views the thread has it it
vale 30000 reproducciones tiene el hilo
was posted not long ago Thank you very much it
lo han publicado no hace
was posted not that long ago
gracias lo han publicado no hace tanto
okay it's been a two TR hours three
vale hará un dos TR horillas tres
hours okay note this thread was made
horillas vale nota este hilo está hecho
by a
por tarada
mentally [ __ ] Lucy And why are you posting it on
mental Lucy Y por qué lo publicas en
another
otra
account follow all those accounts for
cuenta sigan a todas esas cuentas para
updates on this [ __ ] off [ __ ] off I mean
actualizaciones sobre este Vete a la
what's it about I
[__] Vete a la [__] o sea de qué va
mean publish a thread where he's going to denounce
o sea publica un hilo donde va a a funar
Comanche and with a photo of his supposed
a Comanche y con foto de su supuesta
Tula and the first I mean the first tweet
Tula y el primer o sea el primer tweet
is the announcement 100% okay why isn't he going to
es el anuncio 100% vale porque no te va
put that first tweet okay But the
a poner ese primer tweet vale Pero la la
the first part of the thread I mean
la primera parte del hilo o sea el
Lilo's first tweet is spam from four
primer tweet de Lilo es spam de cuatro
people whatever the [ __ ] if you want someone to
personas sea qué [__] si quies alguien
update the topic  you publish on the
actualización del tema lo publicas en la
same
misma
account follow me please but follow me please
cuenta sígueme porfi pero sígueme porfi
if she hasn't missed here that you follow three
si no le ha falta aquí que sigas a tres
friends nothing nothing famita because this already
amigas nada nada famita pues esto ya
looks bad of course with
pinta mal claro con
this it is that with this it looks terrible you
esto es que ya con esto pinta fatal
know No it's not that she has missed here in the
sabes No no es que le ha faltado aquí a
end she plays r shad of Legend
al al final juega r shad of Legend
you know context we were talking normally
sabes contexo estábamos hablando normal
in our GC with four other people
en nuestro GC con otras cuatro personas
and my friend Luciana at one point Luciana
y mi amiga Luciana en un momento Luciana
told us that Comanche spoke to her on
nos dijo que Comanche le habló por
Instagram she is a fan of streamer in
Instagram ella es fan de streamer en
general and before she was a fan of Comanche they are
general y antes era fan de Comanche ya
not a fan anymore So it was very strange okay let's
no esan fan Así que fue muy raro vale a
see girls girls I can't believe it you are
ver chicas chicas eu no lo puedo creer
not going to believe me
no me lo van a creer
God
Dios
help okay because Comanche has
ayuda vale porque Comanche le ha
seen him he has responded to a story of
visto ha respondido a una historia de
hers okay damn It's supposed to
ella vale conche Se supone
Okay here you can see that he reacted to
Okay acá se ve que le que le reaccionó
stories where you only see his
historias donde se le ve únicamente el
body which is strange but it is stranger
cuerpo lo cual es raro pero es más raro
considering that Luciana is 14
teniendo en cuenta que Luciana tiene 14
and he is 27 years old apart Luciana has his
y él 27 años aparte Luciana tiene su
age in her Instagram bio and has a
edad en su bío de Instagram y tiene una
highlight of his 14th birthday he
destacada de su cumpleaños número 14 él
knew it Yeah it's supposed to  that Comanche
lo sabía Ajá se supone que Comanche le
puts fires and puts hearts to
pone fueguitos y le pone corazones a
stories about the girl's body okay
historias del cuerpo de la niña vale
Hi I can't believe it this is the most random thing
Hola No lo puedo creer es lo más Random
that happened to me this whole
que me pasó en todo lo que va del
year at first we didn't believe him With good
año al principio no le creímos Con justa
reason since it is something
razón ya que es algo
very we didn't understand Why out of nowhere
muy no entendíamos Por qué de la nada
com Anchel wrote And why Right to
com anchel escribía Y por qué Justo a
her but it was real and she wasn't
ella pero era real y ella no estaba
lying Comanche had
mintiendo Comanche sí le había
written to her okay Okay inco thanks handsome don't
escrito vale Vale inco gracias guapo no
forget don't forget what you
se me olvide no se me olvide lo que me
told me you don't even believe it yourself on top of that he
dicho no te la crees ni vos encima la
wants to rumble her
quiere grumar
exposed between all of us we told
exposta entre todos le dijimos a
Louisiana Thank you so much I send you a
Luisiana Muchísimas gracias Te mando un
kiss to the current to see what
beso a la corriente para ver qué
intentions he had which were
intenciones tenía las cuales fueron
bad and sick I'm going to leave some
malas y enfermizas voy a dejar algunas
screenshots
capturas a
below I say go with the
continuación yo digo que le sigas la
flow to see if he has bad
corriente a ver si tiene Malas
intentions apart from in your
intenciones aparte en tu descripción de
Instagram description it appears that you are
Instagram aparece que tienes
14 and that you are a minor act nice
14 y que sos menor hacete la buenita
to see his true intentions
para ver sus verdaderas intenciones
maybe the guy is known for being a
igual al chavón lo conocen por ser Un
wanker let's not expect much okay okay
[__] no esperemos mucho
inco We have to be very
vale vale inco Tenemos que tener mucho
careful with the dick of  Comanche today eh I
cuidado con la [__] de Comanche hoy eh
never expected to say this but I'm
nunca esperaba decir esto pero lo estoy
warning you okay We have to be very
avisando vale Tenemos que tener mucho
careful with Comanche's dick
cuidado con la [__] de Comanche esta
tonight This is the beginning of the
noche Este es el inicio de la
conversation where he reacts to the
conversación donde le reacciona las
stories and
historias y le
talks to him we've seen it okay And now
habla lo hemos visto vale Y ahora
the conversations begin for God's sake be
empiezan las conversaciones por Dios
very careful eh Because also here
mucho cuidado eh Porque además aquí
when I open a Pam you see when when
cuando yo abro una Pam veis cuando
I open one here below you see here you
cuando yo abro una aquí abajo veis aquí
are seeing my Twitter user No
estáis viendo mi usuario de Twitter No
well here
pues aquí
below here the next tweet appears
abajo aquí abajo sale el siguiente twit
So when I open here
Así que cuando yo abra aquí va a salir
the apya will appear when I open the previous one
la apya de cuando yo abra el anterior va
the apya of Comanche will appear below
a salir aquí abajo la apya de Comanche
But my window will cover it and in the
Pero la va a tapar mi ventana y en la
vertical one I'm going to move the reaction a little bit
del vertical voy a mover un poquito la
here so that not
reacción para acá para que no se vea ni
a
un píxel de
single pixel can be seen it's not like I'm going to monetize
huevo tampoco es que vaya a monetizar
because of the language I'm having no
por el lenguaje que estoy teniendo no
Hello this is very random but
Hola esto es muy Random pero
Hello is one of those who write that already
Hola es de las que escriben eso ya me
puts me off eh But well she is a
echa para atrás eh Pero bueno es una
kid we are talking about a person of
cría estamos hablando de una persona de
course Hello Why beautiful because s
claro Hola Por qué linda porque s
famous I was in shock when I saw your
famosito me quedé en shock cuando vi tu
note above before You  refan Aba that's why I
noti encima antes Te refan Aba por eso
think it's crazy I don't know Au How pretty they
me parece reloco no sé Au Qué linda ya
are not my fan anymore one question how old are you
no son mi fan una pregunta qué edad
thanks you I don't see you
tienes gracias vos más ya no te veo
as much anymore being H this but sometimes I see you
tanto siendo H esta pero a veces te veo
Yes it's in my
Sí está en mi
vio you really are 14 you look very
vio de verdad tienes 14 te ves muy
pretty for being so little Yes I
bonita para ser tan chiquita Sí de
really turn 15 on December 17th I don't
verdad cumplo 15 el 17 de diciembre no
want to turn 15 the crisis no the the
quiero cumplir 15 la crisis no la la
crisis of 15 No they really are very
crisis de los 15 No de verdad son muy
pretty for being 14 the FBI is going to come for
bonitas para tener 14 el FBI va a venir
me
a por mí
Hehehe you
Jejeje me
surprised me Thank you very much really
sorprendiste Muchas gracias de verdad
you are very
vos está bien
cute and are you going to invite me today it's
lindo y me vas a invitar hoy es
the careful you the incom no No not yet
el cuidado tú la incom no No todavía no
eh I mean we are like in the castle of
eh o sea estamos como en el castillo del
terror like in the castle of terror
terror como en el castillo del terror
there in the dark at the fair not going through
ahí a oscura en la feria no pasando por
the aisles be careful because at any
los pasillos cuidado que en cualquier
moment Comanche's penis will appear
momento nos aparece el pene de Comanche
no no no no worse even worse yet I don't know if I
no no no no peor aún peor aún no sé si
'm going to be able to sleep with the comparison
voy a poder dormir con la comparación
that I'm going to make now the
que os voy a hacer ahora el tren de la
witch train the witch train is like we
bruja el tren de la bruja es como si
were right now
fuéramos ahora
on the witch train and instead
mismo en el tren de la bruja y de en vez
of a  broom let's get a
de un escobazo nos vayamos a llevar un
Comanche dick no dude no no no no
pollazo de Comanche no tío no no no no
mu Thank you very much Welcome remind you
mu Muchas gracias Bienvenido recordaros
all Look at the bar this is yours
a todos Mirad la barra esto es vuestro
eh
eh
3259 members that's yours from my
3259 miembros eso es vuestro de mi
kids from my kids from
chavalería de mis chavales de mis
my kids okay if
chavales de mi chavalería vale si
you want I don't know how many people are there right
ustedes queréis no sé cuánta gente hay
now live because it doesn't
ahora mismo en directo porque no me
appear to me 300 appear but it's
aparece me aparecen 300 pero es del
vertical if you want we reach
vertical si ustedes queréis llegamos a
4000 tonight you each give away my
4000 esta misma noche regaláis mi cada
and we reach 4000 isac isac
uno y llegamos a 4000
we could reach 4000 soon I'm
isac podríamos llegar a 4000 en breves
afraid I'm afraid that
tengo miedo tengo miedo a que no se
the ones that are given away won't be renewed before we
renueven las que sean regaladas antes de
reach 4000 but right now
que lleguemos a los 4000 pero ahora
we have the record number of members
mismo estamos en el récord de miembros
that this channel has
que ha tenido este canal en su
ever had are you going to invite me just in case Come to
vida me vas a invitar por si Vení a
Argentina yes
Argentina
you're from Argentina Every day I confirm
s eres de Argentina Cada día confirmo
more that
más que
they are very good with all due respect eh
están buenísimas con todo respeto eh
But you are perfect young lady short and
Pero eres perfecta joven chiquita y
pretty This seems too
linda Esto me parece demasiado
fake to me Let's see I don't know but it's that either we're
falso A ver no sé pero es que o sea o ya
going to do it or  It seems too false to me or you
s la vamos o me parece demasiado falso o
wrote this damn but come on
esto lo has escrito conche pero vamos
without taking the medication in s 8
sin tomarse la medicación en s 8
months but now it's not that you talk to
meses pero ya ya no es que le hables a
a 14 year old with a certain lack of shame
una de 14 con con cierta poca vergüenza
but since you're saying you're
sino que ya que diciendo estás
emphasizing you know you're emphasizing that
recalcando sabes estás recalcando que
you're a pedophile young girl short and
eres pedófilo joven chiquita y
pretty that doesn't nor does it have any
linda que no tiene ni no tiene ni
sense this doesn't have any sense eh
sentido no tiene ni sentido esto eh
Come on if it's true it seems [ __ ]
Vamos como sea verdad me parece una [__]
crazy to me eh If this is true that I do
locura eh Como esto sea verdad que creo
n't think I thought Because they also emphasize
no pensé Porque además es que recalcan
a lot the age issue
mucho lo del tema de la edad
eh they emphasize a lot the age issue Tula is
eh recalcan mucho lo del tema de la edad
coming eh Tula is coming eh
se viene Tula eh se viene Tula eh
Tula is coming in the next one in the
se viene Tula en la siguiente en la
next
siguiente
publication I'm really nervous because of
publicación estoy estáa nervioso porque
course It's that I can't read your messages right now
claro Es que no puedo leeros ahora mismo
because I have Tula there
los mensajes porque la tengo ahí la Tula
eh I mean I have her there Ah It's false
eh o sea es que la tengo ahí Ah Es falso
I would swear that this is false
Yo juraría que esto es falso
yes I don't know either Put your hand in the
sí no lo sé tampoco Pon la mano en el
fire but it seems to me that she emphasizes
fuego pero es que me parece que hace
too much I didn't think it
como demasiado hincapié no pensé que te
would bother you that she was 14 years old the
iba a molestar que tuviera 14 años la
truth I say You are already an older man they take
verdad digo Vos ya s es un hombre mayor
me out  many years another little question have you
me sacan muchos años otra preguntita has
had a boyfriend or something similar Why would it
tenido novio o algo similar Por qué me
bother me It's that this is
molestaría Es que esto es
too much this is too much why would I get
demasiado esto es demasiado por qué me
upset over nothing because you are 27
molestaría por nada porque tienes 27
years old and she is 14 nothing maybe for many it is
años y ella 14 nada quizás para muchos
wrong but I do not see anything wrong with it
esté mal pero yo no le veo nada de malo
Ah this can't be
Ah es que esto no puede ser
true This can't be true
verdad Esto no puede ser
normally normally H it can't
verdad normalmente normalmente H no
be true normally when a
puede ser verdad normalmente cuando un
streamer is like this the groomer okay
streamer es así la del groomer vale
normally what she does is like
normalmente lo que hace es como
Eh she doesn't want to deal with the age issue
Eh no quiere tratar el tema de la edad
much No she doesn't put much emphasis on
mucho No no hace mucho hincapié en
conversations on the age issue you
conversaciones en el tema de la edad
know or nothing you are lying you are not
sabes o nada tú estás mintiendo tú no
that age I don't know what you know I don't know
tienes esa edad no sé qué sabes No lo sé
something else Okay it's too much emphasis Yes
otra cosa Vale es demasiado hincapié Sí
yes it's that she is telling him it's that it's like it's
sí es que ella le está diciendo es que
very prepared it's like very
es que es como muy preparado es como muy
prepared it's like say that you don't give a
preparado es como di que te importa una
[ __ ] that she's 14 and that you know that she's
[__] que tenga 14 y que tú sabes que
14 but that you care a little
tiene 14 pero que te importa un poco
because you are a pedophile It's that she has been missing
porque eres pedófilo Es que le ha falta
here to say nothing I don't care I like to
aquí decir nada no me importa me gusta
be a little pederast Okay and and I usually I
ser un poco pederasta Vale y y suelo
usually go for minors that's what is
suelo entrarle a menores es lo que le
missing here the
falta aquí el
message you see let's go is that if this is
mensaje se veas vamos es que si esto es
true that  Obviously I wouldn't put my
verdad que evidentemente yo no pongo la
hand in the fire for anyone okay but if
mano en el fuego por nadie vale pero de
this is
ser esto
true come on damn it no Taking the
verdad vamos conche que no Toma las
pills in your [ __ ]
pastillas en la [__]
life it's a promotion for her next
vida es una promoción para su próximo
single your age has nothing to do with it
sencillo tu edad no tiene nada que ver
you are still very
tú sigues siendo muy
pretty really I think you are pretty
linda de verdad Me pareces bonita
Even if you are
Incluso si tienes
14 no no no Then you are a virgin
14 que no que no Entonces sos virgen
right eh Yeah why that not very
verdad eh Sí por qué esa pregunta nada
nice question just to make sure you are the
bonita solo para asegurarme de que seas
right one I have
correcta
n't even had a boyfriend but yes I
ni siquiera he tenido novio pero sí lo
really am I think you are pretty I want you to
soy de verdad me pare linda quiero que
believe me Ugh Tula is coming I have
me creas Uf se viene la Tula tengo ahí
all of Comanche's [ __ ] right there next to me
todo el pollón de Comanche ahí al lado
with super black balls
con los [__] super negros
man What a danger that suddenly my
tío Qué peligro de que de repente se me
camera goes
vaya la cámara
eh the only thing is if it is false who knows
eh lo único que si es falso a saber de
where they got the photo of Tula
dónde han sacado la foto de la Tula
maybe it is even the boyfriend of one of
quizá hasta es del novio de alguna de
them we would have to ask
ellas le tendríamos que preguntar
some of some of those on Twitter if it is the one
algunos de algunos de Twitter si es la
from
de
Dallas some of those on Twitter who want
Dallas algunos de Twitter que quieren el
Dallas' dick okay we would have to
[__] de Dallas vale tendríamos que
ask her if it is the one from Dallas at
preguntarle si si es la de Dallas por lo
least to make sure or
menos para asegurarnos o
not are you going to send me money or what But go ahead I
no me vas a mandar plata o qué Pero dale
accept I have nothing to lose send her
acepto no tengo nada que perder le manda
the photo
la foto
takes a screenshot and says now you think I'm
le saca captura y dice ahora me crees
pretty but it really strikes me
linda pero me llama mucho la atención
that she also takes the screenshot
que además la captura de pantalla la
but crops it and normally
saca pero la recorta además normalmente
when you take a
cuando tú Vas sacando captura de
screenshot you get the whole phone,
pantalla te sale todo el móvil completo
Comanche's Instagram not with the
el el Instagram de Comanche no con el
verified pam pam pam pam you know and
verificado pam pam pam pam sabes y te
have you bothered to crop the screenshot
has molestado en recortar la captura
so that neither the top of the
para que no se vea ni lo de arriba de la
screenshot nor the
captura ni lo de
bottom can be seen
abajo
friend who was disgusting seriously I didn't ask you to
amigo que puso asco en serio no te pedí
send me a picture of your dick
que me mandaras una foto de tu pija
I thought you were going to like it Don't get really mad if you're
Pensé que te iba a gustar No te enojes
sick you better have it or whatever Or whatever
enfermo mejor que tengas o sea O sea ya
the girl reacts badly I don't
además la chica le reacciona mal no lo
buy this gaya a kiss now the girl
compro esto gaya un beso ya la chica
reacts badly and he still responds
reacciona mal y él todavía le responde
having sent her his dick knowing that they will
habiéndole mandado la [__] sabiendo que
[ __ ] him and that this and that this is going to be
lo funan y que esto y que esto lo van a
published on Twitter he responds better
publicar en Twitter é le respond mejor
if you are 14 That's how you learn when you're
que tengas 14 Así vas aprendiendo de
little go on man go on man no man no no I'm
pequeña anda hombre anda hombre que no
not going to take the
hombre que no que no voy a quitar la
screen off for a
pantalla un
second
segund
Pam bread okay just in
Pam pan vale por si
case just in case because
acaso por si acaso porque me ha dicho
Inc Sky told me to go to his
Inc Sky que me vaya a su
Twitter  that there is
Twitter que hay
something that can help me see
algo que me puede resar a ver dato
extra information okay there is a
extra vale hay una [__]
pixelated dick Comanche is not really
pixelada Comanche no es realmente
skinny yes But it could be a thing of the photo
flaco sí Pero puede ser cosa de la foto
okay maybe at the beginning a video uploaded
vale sea al principio un vídeo subido
by
por
them
ellas
Yeah okay a video you mean this
Ajá vale un vídeo te refieres a este
video I can't put it there are no penises I
vídeo no lo puedo poner no hay penes
can't
no lo puedo
put it there are no penises no okay let's
poner no hay penes no vale a
see I understand that there are no penises No it's not
ver entiendo que no hay penes No aquí no
worth it here it's a video uploaded by
vale es un vídeo subido por
them with the conversations El
ellas con las conversaciones El
Comanche let's
Comanche a
see I wouldn't know how to check this let's
ver No sabría yo cómo comprobar esto a
see
ver
elco El Comanche
elco El Comanche
Yeah
Ajá
okay here in this video it seems real
vale aquí en este vídeo parece real
no
no
And what date is it from let's
Y de qué fecha
see here here of course here it seems
datara a ver aquí aquí claro aquí parece
very real No here we found some
muy real No aquí en encontramos algún
fault here mikutis a kiss Thank you very much
fallo aquí mikutis un beso Muchas
welcome we found some fault here
bienvenido encontramos algún fallo aquí
in sight family Well look it loads no
a la vista familia Pues mira carga no
when it's uploading it's
cuando va subiendo va
loading
cargando
or rather here the possibility would be that it
o sea aquí la posibilidad sería de que
was a
fuera una una
conversation if it were fake it
conversación si fuera falso
couldn't be perfectly the same
no podría ser perfectamente que lo mismo
no that Comanche's profile photo is put
no que se pone la foto de perfil de
and that they take the top part
Comanche y que la parte de arriba la
from Comanche but the bottom part
cogen de Comanche pero la parte de abajo
no no okay I'm going to remove it I'm going to see what
no no vale voy a quitar voy a ver qué
else there is I'm
más
going  let's see what else there is I'm
voy a ver qué más
going to see what else there is there is
hay voy a ver qué más
an error Ah It's true there is an
hay que hay un error Ah Es verdad hay un
error it's true there is an error here Ramón
error es verdad hay aquí un error Ramón
Today is the
Hoy es el
day one of the errors that I find
día uno de los fallos que yo encuentro
is that in that type of photo that
es que en ese tipo de foto que
Comanche supposedly sends if you
supuestamente manda Comanche si uno le
take a screenshot the application warns that you
saca captura la aplicación avisa que
took a screenshot and next to it appears a
sacaste captura y al lado sale un
symbol of the screenshot taken But it did
símbolo de la captura tomada Pero eso sí
have that now I'll
lo tenía ahora os lo
put it for you I remember that Comanche in your
pongo recuerdo que Comanche en tu
interview stressed that when he flirts he is
entrevista recalcó que cuando liga es
so careful with age that it is even
tan cuidadoso con la edad que incluso es
the first thing he asks it would seem strange to me if
lo primero que pregunta se me haría raro
it were
que fuera
real they say that the photo looks badly
real dicen que la foto se mira mal
cut the
cortada la de
profile photo badly
la de perfil mal
cut Look here the error that inco has put look
cortada Mira aquí el fallo que ha puesto
here
inco mira que aquí aparece
this appears and Here you do
esto y Aquí
n't see
no
here
veis aquí aparece
this appears and in this other one for whatever reason
esto y en esta otra por lo que sea
no I don't know what explanation there would be here
no no sé qué explicación habría que aquí
if there was one
si la
and here
hubiera y aquí
not but what it tells me yes it shows that the
no pero lo que lo que me dice sí que
iPhone emojis appear the fact that if the second I mean
iPhone el hecho de que si ap la segunda
the iPhone emojis appear
O sea que aparecen los emojis de iPhone
and it's not an iPhone is it
y no es un iPhone es
true yes the last video of pepino Andy
verdad sí el último vídeo de pepino Andy
that I don't
que no se me
forget is
olvide es
true is it true you  eh the emojis are from
verdad es verdad tú eh los emojis son de
iPhone and it's not an
iPhone y no es un
iPhone it's
iPhone es
true Let's see see I
verdad A ver
want you to believe me okay look look you
Mira Quiero que me creas vale
see it here is the photo bomb Ah It
mira lo veis aquí está la foto bomba Ah
's true It's true when you take a
Es verdad Es verdad cuando se le hace
screenshot here it appears like a little circle
captura aquí aparece como un circulito
I would swear I had seen it in the screenshot
juraría que lo había visto en la captura
but it doesn't appear here it's true look
pero aquí no sale es verdad mira
you know the little circle that appears when you
sabéis el circulito que aparece cuando
take screenshots It's true the little mark that
salen capturas Es verdad la marquita que
Instagram puts on you Oh [ __ ] No I'm
te pone Instagram Ay [__] Que no Estoy
sharing the screen I'm an idiot
compartiendo la pantalla que soy idiota
man here you see the bomb it's a photo that you
tío aquí veis la bomba es una foto que
can only see once But
solamente la puedes ver una vez Pero
when the person takes a screenshot it
cuando la persona saca captura te
appears here like some dots like
aparece aquí como unos puntitos como
some
unas
lines okay luare But that's for the
rayitas vale luare Pero eso es para el
news more than anything dude I see it more
noti más que nada tío lo lo veo yo más
for the news Ha but the other time in the
para noti Ja pero la otra vez en el
debate you took out the Tula and papee aibel
debate te sacaste la Tula y papee aibel
But that has that here only that it was
Pero eso que tiene que aquí only que era
the Tula of the photo let's see the emojis
la Tula de la foto a ver los los emojis
are from
son de
iPhone I ask because I don't know if the
iPhone pregunto porque yo no sé si los
emo can be from other
emos pueden ser de de otr
devices
dispositivos
the emojis are from
los emojis son de
iPhone are you
iPhone me estáis
telling me or can they also be from
diciendo o pueden ser también de de
any other
cualquier otro
phone are they unique to
teléfono son únicos de
iPhone okay well here  the top part
iPhone vale pues aquí la parte de arriba
is from
es de
Android what nonsense Well if you're going to do it
Android que qué tontería Pues si lo vas
right Why are you going to do one
a hacer bien Por qué vas a hacer una
part on the iPhone and another part on the
parte en el iPhone y otra parte en el
No well come on if he did
No pues vamos si ha hecho
this what nonsense no let's see I think
esto qué tontería no a ver yo creo que
this is false m the truth
esto es falso m la verdad
eh It is that I think it's
eh Es que creo que es
false so I am false so false
falso so soy falso so falso
Comanche has responded to Lilo
Comanche puesto ha contestado al Lilo
okay And he says the lawsuit that they are going to
vale Y dice la demanda que se van a
take for
llevar por
spreading false information I will be a
difundir información falsa seré un
joker but not a
cachondo pero no un
fart okay that has been Comanche's response
pedo vale esa ha sido la respuesta de
to the thread funa
Comanche al al hilo funa
okay I personally think it's false
vale yo personalmente creo que es falso
go up to Comanche and then the girls Javi let's
sube a Comanche y luego las chicas Javi
see I think the intention was to gain
a ver yo creo que la intención era ganar
followers man I mean I think it has been
seguidores tío o sea yo creo que ha sido
a really disgusting thing to
una cosa asquerosísimo
gain followers and that's it
para ganar seguidores y punto que
don't
no
move that ass move that ass Come on come on move
muéveme ese culo muéveme ese culo Dale
that ass Come on move to Come on
dale mueve ese culo Dale mueve to Dale
[Music]
[Música]
mu up down up
mu arriba abajo arriba
down very good perfect let's go
abajo muy bien perfecto vamos
mess
lío
slip welcome welcome slip Welcome let's
slip bienvenido bienvenido slip
see They tell me that the moror has
ver Me comentan que el moror me ha
insulted me and uncle
insultado a mí y al tío
Sur okay I haven't seen it I'm going to see it he
Sur vale No lo he visto lo voy a ver he
posted here some eh well i
puesto por aquí algunas Eh bueno he
posted a thread here in which
puesto por aquí un hilo en el que
basically
básicamente
eh the
eh empiezan a discutir en Twitter el
moror and uncle Sur start arguing on Twitter but that will be in
moror y el tío Sur pero eso va a ser en
another excerpt okay first i'm going to see what
otro extracto vale primero voy a ver qué
the
es lo que ha dicho el
active moror said since right now i just
moror activo que ahora mismo acabo de
started and now i know that being far
empezar y ahora sé que estando muu
behind not a single video is going to fail
detrás no va a fallar ni un solo vídeo
never ever they start in march the classes there
nunca jamás arrancan en marzo las clases
were like 30 the guy was wearing a hat and
había como 30 el tipo lleó con gorro y
a hooded jacket we were watching and
una campera con capucha nosotros mir y
this special and the teacher says Okay i'm going
este especial y la profe dice Bueno voy
to go to a classmate Oh wait a sec a sec You're welcome a sec You're welcome my audio is a bit messed up it happens to me sometimes but by touching a little key here it can be fixed in a moment Oh it's just
clavita se arregla en un momento Ah es
that it fell over there how
que se ha caído por ahí como se ha caído
this fell wait because here it's going to take me
esto espérate porque aquí voy a tener
longer
que tardar más un momento
man
tío
yeah but come on
ya pero vamos
wanting this i don't throw it away come on oh
esto queriendo no lo tir vamos madre
my god oh my god okay unin you're welcome you're welcome you're welcome you're welcome
mía madre
eh it won't take
nada eh no tardo
long this
nada
bit and i'll post it
poito y lo pongo
and in
y en
theory it's good because it has okay it just
teoría bien porque tiene vale se acaba
solve ok perfect it's just
solucionar vale perfecto se acaba de
solved we started the exo I don't know
solucionar empezamos al exo no sé por
why that happens sometimes with how much I
qué pasa eso algunas veces con con lo
like the
que me gustan los
speakers it
altavoces
happens sometimes but oh well you touch the
pasa algunas veces pero bueno se toca la
plug and it fixes it let's
clavija y se arregla a
see if it sounds good
ver se escucha bien
guys Hi hi hi it sounds
chicos Hola hola hola se escucha
good
bien
ok all good Hi hi it sounds good let's see
vale todo bien Hola hola se escucha bien
I'm missing so that it sounds
a ver Me faltan para que se escuche
perfect I'm missing five members of
perfecto me faltan cinco miembros de
each of those who are
cada uno de los que estáis ahora mismo
in the chat right now Let's see five members of
en el chat A ver cinco miembros de cada
each of those who are in the chat I'm
uno de los que estáis en el chat me
missing eh so that it sounds better ok let's
falta eh para que se escuche mejor vale
see as I was saying I saw that
a ver como iba diciendo he visto que el
mill just argued with uncle sh on
mill ahora ha discutido con el tío sh en
Twitter ok but that will be another
Twitter vale pero eso ya será otro
excerpt First I want to see what
extracto Primero quiero ver lo que ha
millor said because they've told me that he
dicho el millor porque me han dicho que
messes with me also with me with
se mete conmigo también conmigo con
Dallas with uncle shur with delox Okay
Dallas con el tío shur con el delox Vale
then we're going to listen to it and I'll give my
entonces lo vamos a escuchar y daré una
opinion most likely I'll
opinión muy probablemente os voy
announce it I'm going to take off my wings I'm going to get
anunciando me voy a quitar las alajas me
comfortable I'm going to get comfortable
cómodo me vo poniendo cómodo
probably I
probablemente
'll announce it to you now I've already told you
os lo voy anunciando ya ya os he dicho
that the main channel is going to
que en el canal principal se van a
resume the videos okay And such Ah most
retomar los vídeos vale Y tal Ah muy
likely  You're going to have a video of the
probablemente Vais a tener un vídeo del
best who says a video of the best
millor quien dice un vídeo del millor
says a series it's that there are several things out
dice una serie es que hay varias cosas
there that are accumulating they are
por ahí que se van acumulando se van
accumulating No man gain over Let's see no
acumulando No hombre gain over A ver no
G over as
G over como
such well I don't know eh it could it could be
tal bueno no lo sé eh podría podría ser
a Game Over No man let's see I don't know if the
un Game Over No hombre a ver no sé si el
best has that importance to
millor tiene esa importancia como para
call it Game Over that repercussion
llamarlo Game Over esa repercusión
although there has also been Random eh in
aunque también ha habido Random eh en
Game Over eh but video No no Let's see I don't
Game Over eh pero vídeo No no A ver no
know if I would call it gameover once it's
sé si lo llamaría gameover una vez que
finished we would see but yes it
esté terminado ya lo veríamos pero sí
is true that a video is coming a
que es verdad que se viene vídeo un
video of the
vídeo del
best a video of the best probably
millor un vídeo del millor probablemente
in the next few days weeks I don't know
en los próximos días semanas no sé
when exactly okay because
cuándo exactamente vale porque
now We are going back to the videos of the
ahora Estamos volviendo los vídeos del
main Channel today we uploaded This one okay
principal hoy hemos subido Este vale
about Nayib Bukele who wants to rescue
sobre nayib bukele que quiere rescatar
Haiti wants to save Haiti and then there's
Haití quiere salvar Haití y después se
a video of Kate Midelton that is
viene un vídeo de Kate midelton que está
recorded the editor is also with him m
grabado también está el editor con él m
then there's another video about
luego se viene otro vídeo sobre
Nickelodeon okay there are several videos in the
Nickelodeon vale hay varios vídeos en
list there are several videos in the queue okay
lista hay varios vídeos en cola vale
But there will be videos of youtubers
Pero va a haber vídeos de youtubers
also on the main channel of the
también en el canal principal de los de
usual ones okay our
siempre vale nuestro
seal I don't know I don't know if it will be  a video yes it
sello No sé no sé si será un vídeo si
will be a series But there are several things there
será una serie Pero hay varias cosas ahí
of the millor that we have to comment on okay it
del millor que tenemos que comentar vale
may even be some in
pueden que sea incluso algunas en
response to whatever he tells us Here I
respuesta a lo que sea que nos diga Aquí
also tell you okay But that's why be
también os digo vale Pero por eso estar
very aware of the Main Channel
muy pendiente del Canal principal
subscribe to the Main Channel jav
suscribiros al Canal principal jav
oliveira
oliveira
and subscribe above all subscribe and
y suscribiros sobre todo suscribiros y
support the videos okay support the videos
apoyar los vídeos vale apoyar los vídeos
Micaela just gave away five members
Micaela acaba de regalar cinco miembros
a round of applause from the entire chat for Micaela
un aplauso de todo el chat para Micaela
a kiss a kiss Thank you so much
un beso un beso Muchísimas gracias
Micaela we love you Micaela a kiss
Micaela te queremos Micaela un beso
beautiful she will not fail a single video
guapa no va a fallar ni un solo vídeo
never ever the classes start in March there
nunca jamás arrancan en marzo las clase
were like 30 and the guy arrived with gold and
había como 30 y el tipo llegó con oro y
a hooded jacket we looked and
una campera con capucha nosotros mir y
this special and the teacher says Well I'm going
este especial y la profe dice Bueno voy
to buy a classmate to take him well because he has
a prar un compañero trlo bien porque
autism I don't know what I said it It's
tiene tiene autismo no sé qué yo lo dije
okay there are people who deserve it there are
Está bien hay gente que se merece hay
people who have to forge their personality
gente que hay que forjar la personalidad
And make them change their minds whether they want it
Y hacerle que cambie de opinión quieran
or not In the absence of strict upbringing from
o no A falta de una crianza estricta de
their parents, character is formed if you are not
sus padres forma carácter si tú no eres
a strict parent with your child believe me
un padre estricto con tu hijo créeme que
society will instill those
la sociedad le va a inculcar esos
values ​​​​in them  of blows and you don't
valores a base de golpes y eso no te
like that I'm 100% sure that the
gustar Estoy 100% seguro que a los
four of them were bullied at school I'd bet
cuatro les hacían en el cole apostaría
a lot I'd bet hard that they
mucho apostaría fuerte a que pocos
ate few sandwiches none of these
bocadillos se comían ninguno de de estos
four few uh few sandwiches were
cuatro pocos eh pocos bocadillos se
eaten in the schoolyard going out to the
comían en el patio del colegio salido al
bathroom
baño
going but well let's see the best is the
yando pero bueno a ver el millor es que
same eh He diagnoses you or not If
lo mismo eh Te diagnostica o no Si
you have some type of mental illness or you don't
tienes algún tipo de enfermedad mental o
have it eh I mean suddenly the
no la tienes eh o sea de repente el
best okay if a person comes out and says that they have
millor vale si sale una persona y cuenta
had a suicide attempt Well
que ha tenido un intento autolítico Pues
the best tells you no that you haven't
el millor te dice que no que no lo has
had it that what you have is
tenido que lo que tienes es
retardation okay because he knows it And
retraso vale porque él lo sabe Y
so
entonces
here what are you basing it on yes they look like
aquí en qué te basas sí que tienen pinta
they have been bullied But
de que les han hecho bullying Pero por
why for the
qué por el
comment for the comment that they have been
comentario por el
bullied
comentario de que les han hecho bullying
man I saw the comment more that it
hombre yo el comentario lo vi más que c
cited bullying more than that It
itaba al bullying más que que se lo
might have been done to them no I mean a
Hubieran hecho a ellos no O sea una
person when a person who goes through
persona cuando una persona que pasa por
bullying I understand that has two
el bullying entiendo que tiene dos
ways of reacting afterwards to
formas de de reaccionar después a la
life is worth one It's that suddenly they do it a
vida vale una Es que de repente lo hace
lot is worth like in revenge to the world in
mucho vale como en venganza al mundo en
revenge to life
venganza a la vida
eh but the most logical but of course the
eh pero lo lo más lógico pero claro el
human being many times does not act by
ser humano muchas veces no actúa por la
logic no man the most logical thing is that
lógica no hombre lo más Lógico es que
knowing what suf del millor Dallas
sabiendo lo que suf del millor Dallas
versus revenant is Random a kiss is
versus revenant es Random un beso es
true That that its peak is true my
verdad Ese ese su pico es verdad mi
peak my most viewed live I think it was
pico mi directo más visto creo que fue
with Antonia Avin my live with the most
con Antonia avin mi directo con más
viewers I think it was with
espectadores creo que ha sido con
Antonia Avin not the most viewed because
Antonia avin no el más visto porque
then in the salsería I have live shows with
luego en la salsería tengo directos con
more than a million views I think I
más de un millón de visitas creo que
have like three I've had like three or
tengo como tres he tenido como tres o
four thousand like three or four live shows
cuat mill como tres o cuatro directos
with more than more than a million
con más de con más de un millón de
views okay In fact two of them have
visitas vale De hecho dos de ellos han
had almost 2 million views but
tenido casi 2 millones de visitas pero
from Peak viewer
de Pico de espectador
the most viewed was Antonio David's I
el más visto fue el de Antonio David
think and then the one I did with
creo y luego el que hice con
Frano here I wouldn't dare to sign if
frano aquí no me atrevería a firmar si
the four of them have suffered bullying No I
han sufrido bullying los cuatro No yo
only follow my king Javi the crab
solo sigo a mi rey Javi el cangrejo gra
thank you very much a kiss handsome we
muchísimas gracias un beso guapísimo se
love you Ah what I made a tremendous joke here
quiere Ah lo que peg una vacilada aquí
and a dream allow me okay And I'm
tremenda y una soada permitírmelo vale Y
really sorry okay let people take it
lo siento mucho vale que se lo tome la
however they want I don't give a damn  [ __ ] But
peña como quiera me suda la [__] Pero
what I do have to tell you is that
lo que sí que os tengo que decir es que
the clip was an outrage okay The
el clip era una barbaridad vale Ya las
explanations have already been given we are not
explicaciones están dadas no vamos a
going to go back in much less okay The explanations that have been given are useful to me because in the end it is a way of patching it up and that's it okay eh But what is true is that the clip was an outrage so that you jump on all kinds of alarms but
saltas en cualquier tipo de alarmas pero
come on I say something like this here
vamos yo digo una cosa así aquí en
live and that It will come out tomorrow in the
directo y eso Sale mañana en los
newspapers OK And these four have an
periódicos OK Y estos cuatros tienen una
audience that yes 30 40,000 visits
audiencia que sí que 30 40.000 visitas
the talk show had but it is 30 40,000
tenía la tertulia pero son 30 40.000
visits And 10,000 viewers that
visitas Y 10.000 espectadores que
surely added up between the four
seguramente sumaban entre los cuatro
live shows that none of them found
directos que a ninguno le pareció
the clip scandalous okay And
escandaloso el clip vale Y
that the clip has gone unnoticed for a
que ha pasado desapercibido durante una
week Okay it goes unnoticed and
semana el clip Okay pasa desapercibido y
and we here in a live show without
y nosotros aquí en un directo sin ni
even uploading an excerpt about it
siquiera subir extracto sobre eso lo
we comment on it and it goes viral it makes my
comentamos y se hace viral me suba la
dick hard call me arrogant call me whatever you
[__] llamarme sobrado llamarme lo que
want But oh well You're welcome for going viral
queráis Pero bueno De nada por viralizar
a topic eh Javi But look if
un tema eh Javi Pero mira que si no lo
d ibel and the other one hadn't said it,
dice d ibel y el otro se lo hubieran ido
man, but I already know that That's how it is eh, I mean,
hombre pero eso ya lo sé Eso es así eh o
if that same one, if this same thing says
sea si ese mismo si esto mismo lo dice
Dallas, but it's not that if this same thing
Dallas pero no es que si esto mismo lo
says Dallas It's that later I find out that
dice Dallas Es que luego me entero que
gibel has been threatening roldier
el gibel ha estado amenazando a rold
that I may like roldier more or less and
que me puede caer mejor o peor roldier y
evidently we've had our
evidentemente hemos tenido nuestras
stories and there's the game over that I have
historias y ahí está el game over que
from roldier but man, don't [ __ ] with me, don't
tengo de roldier pero hombre no me jodas
[ __ ] with me that you threatened roldier
no me jodas que has amenazado a roldier
this same week or a couple of months ago, I do
esta misma semana o hace un par de meses
n't know when, but come on, recently you
no sé cuándo pero vamos hace poco has
threatened roldier and you're and you
amenazado a roldier y me estás y me
're telling me that it seems terrible to you that
estás diciendo que te parece fatal que
he threatens Ricky
el da las amenace a Ricky
Eddy, they are in a group, they are like little animals
Eddy están en grupo son como animalitos
like Sprint and his friends, it's because their
como Sprint y sus amiguitos es porque su
audience is not crystal. Well, me, more than
audiencia no es cristal Bueno yo más que
because their audience is not crystal, I
porque su audiencia no sea Cristal Yo
think that Ah, I don't want to get into
creo que Ah es que no quiero entrar en
that,
eso
[ __ ], I think that's the type of profile
[__] Yo creo que es el tipo de perfil
that they have in the audience, they are the
que tienen en la audiencia ya está son
profile of people who, well, those who are not
perfil de gente que bueno a las que no
scandalized by Rich the critic
le de escandalizarse clí Rich el crítico
lamentable in his last video Angel And in
lamentable en su último vídeo Angel Y en
which one not And in which one in his last in his
cuál no Y en cuál en su último en su
first in his second in his
primero en su segundo en su
third laugh I still think the same thing I
tercero risa Sigo pensando lo mismo que
've defended other times that you have to
he defendido otras veces que has de
learn what your place is okay uncle shur
aprender cuál es tu lugar vale tío shur
what he does well is neutrality not give
lo que hace bien es neutralidad no dar
his opinion expose eh the gossip of the
su opinión exponer eh los salseos del
day people like him they like what he does
día a la gente le cae bien le gusta lo
keep the formula You don't have to
que hace mantén la fórmula No tienes por
want more you're having a lot of
qué querer más estás teniendo muchas
visits you're having money he must be
visitas estás teniendo dinero debe estar
billing well uncle shur each month that's it do
facturando bien tío shur al mes ya está
n't want more nobody wants to see what
no quieras más nadie quiere ver lo que
Uncle shur has to say about something okay the
El tío shur tiene que decir sobre algo
same happens with the others the other
va sí Igual pasa con los otros las otras
three or let's see this is very free but
tres u a ver muy gratuito esto pero
let's have the best say it eh it's
vamos que lo diga el millor eh es
pathetic Look let's see
patético Mira a ver
eh point number is that it has its part, I mean
eh punto número es que tiene su parte o
I think that part of Uncle
sea yo creo que parte del éxito del tío
Shur's success is when he leaves his main channel and he
shur cuando deja su canal principal y y
dedicates himself only to a newscast
se dedica únicamente a un noticiero
where he simply gives you the information and
donde Simplemente te da la información y
people come in to see the information
la gente entra para ver la información
without more like candre okay without more without
sin más como candre vale sin más sin
nuances okay no like maybe me for
matices vale no como a lo mejor yo por
example is that I can't avoid it I'll
ejemplo es que yo no puedo evitarlo yo
give you a Nuance  I'm making a comment
te hago un Matiz te hago un comentario
here, a comment there because I can't
aquí un comentario allá porque no puedo
avoid it, otherwise it's not my channel, you
evitarlo que si no no es mi canal me
understand, I try to give all the
entiendes intento dar toda la
information, I try to make the news,
información intento que los noticieros A
unlike the videos and the
diferencia de los vídeos y de los
excerpts, more objective. But anyway,
extractos sean como más objetivos Pero
some comments here and there fall to you,
bueno algún comentar ito por ahí te cae
okay, but of course, part of the key to
vale pero claro parte de la clave del
success. I think that's it, no. I mean, the
éxito Yo creo que es eso no O sea la
news, I want to go in and see what
noticia yo quiero entrar a ver qué es lo
Agustín Rubius aroyit and
que ha dicho Agustín Rubius aroyit y el
Mariana said. I want to go in and see, uh, what he
Mariana Yo quiero entrar a ver eh qué es
said. I want to go in and see
lo que ha dicho yo quiero entrar a ver
the news compilation of the day, what
la recopilación de noticias del día lo
Ari said, what Agustín said, what such and such he
que ha dicho Ari lo que ha dicho Agustín
said, what the guy
lo que ha dicho tal lo que opina el tío
sh thinks, I don't give a damn, it's a little bit,
sh me la suda es un poco
I think the key to success and
el yo creo que la clave del éxito y
besides, I think it's his idea that it should be like that,
aparte creo que es su idea que fuera así
okay, I think it is, I think his, I think it's
vale creo que es creo que su creo que es
his idea,
su idea
and that's it, you
e
know, nobody wants to
y ya está sabes que nadie quiere
listen to what Uncle Sur has to say,
escuchar lo que tiene que decir el tío
man, let's see, he has 10,000, 2,000
Sur hombre a ver tiene 10000 2000
viewers on his live shows. No, if I'm not
espectadores en sus directos No si no me
mistaken,
equivoco
no, the other day I saw him, he had 15 around there.
no el otro día yo lo vi tenía 15 por ahí
No, it's not that  if it goes
No no es que le vaya
wrong then I understand that it will have its
mal entonces entiendo que sí tendrá su
audience who is interested in hearing
público a quien sí le interese escuchar
things as Uncle Sur comments it,
las cosas como la comenta el tío Sur
okay?
vale
Eh
Eh
no and then the discussion has its
no y luego la tertulia tiene sus
viewers too, no then I
espectadores también no entonces
understand that I understand that there will be people who
entiendo que entiendo que Habrá gente a
care not what these
la que le importe no lo que digan los
four say no or
cuatro estos no o
what for the same as the best nobody is
qué pores lo mismo que el millor a nadie
interested beyond those who
le interesa más allá de los que le
follow him who are the same as him
siguen que son igual que él
man There we
hombre Ahí
go and I appreciated this the other day
vamos y esto lo aprecié el otro día
eh Ah that it is a
eh Ah que es un canal
new channel this is a
nuevo esto es un canal
new channel This is the Twitch channel and what
nuevo Este es el canal de Twitch y cuál
is the YouTube channel of the
es el canal de YouTube del
best No no yes it is that I had seen that
millor No no sí es que había visto que
the best was SS sad songs I
el millor estaba SS canciones tristes le
was making the thumbnails for the
estaba haciendo las miniaturas al
best you know and I had seen the visits that it
millor sabes y había visto las visitas
had
que tenía
but of course these subscribers are not no it
pero claro estos suscriptores no son no
is that this channel is not has deleted the
es que este canal no es ha borrado el
other channel or
otro canal o
what By that rule of three the best do not
qué Por esa regla de tres el millor no
get involved in giving your opinion and play
te metas a opinar y juega
LoL
LoL
Yes exactly Lili that is what I was
Sí exactamente Lili a eso es a lo que
going for people you know what you can
iba personas sabes qué es lo que puedes
offer in that you are better than the rest and do
ofrecer en que eres mejor que el resto y
not try to get into things that are
no intentar meterte en cosas en las que
not yours  well the same thing has happened
no se te da bien le ha pasado por
to delox for example you know delox
ejemplo lo mismo a delox sabes delox
was also very good at making
también era como muy bueno haciendo
neutral and objective podcasts and since he
podcast neutrales y objetivos y desde
started giving his opinion well he's not doing it anymore
que está dando su opinión pues ya no le
also you know when you have
está diendo también sabes cuando tienes
a podcast you have to maintain
un podcast has de mantener una
extreme objectivity and extreme neutrality it's
objetividad extrema y una neutralidad
supposed that now it's going badly or rather
del se supone que ahora le va mal o sea
the podcast is not supposed to have had
el podcast no se supone que ha habido
any changes in the podcast let's see
algún cambio en el podcast a ver
the first podcast salo mundo 2.7
el primer podcast salo mundo 2,7
million the second crypto spine eh
millones el segundo crypto spine eh
229000 Ricky's
229000 el de Ricky
1,700000 Dallas's 1,600 plus 1 million
1,700000 el de Dallas 1,600 más 1 millón
apart from Agustín's 51 600000 the one from the
aparte el de Agustín 51 600000 el del
millionor 400000 Stick's 1 300,000
millor 400000 el de Stick 1 300,000
tiparraco 600,000 eh 1 million almost from the
tiparraco 600.000 eh 1 millón casi de lo
virus such and such René half a million micke
de virus tal tal René medio millón micke
crack 4 million
crack 4 millones
eh miso
eh miso
300,000 windy 1 million Willy Red 2
300.000 windy 1 millón Willy Red 2
and a half million these people have
millones y medio esta gente han sido
always been a success all half a million the
siempre un éxito todo medio millón el
second of  Ricky Edi is going for a
segundo de Ricky Edi va va para el
million almost
millón ya casi
H I
H
understand that the latter have fewer
entiendo que estos últimos tienen menos
views because of the guest issue almost or
visitas por el tema del invitado casí o
not I mean
no O sea
eh Because I'm supposed to see if I'm
eh Por se supone que a ver si lo estoy
getting it, it's supposed that the millor is
pillando se supone que el millor está
insinuating point number one that delox's
insinuando punto número uno que a delox
podcast is going badly or point number two
el podcast le va mal o punto número dos
that it's because delos comes
que se debe a que a que el delos venga
here to give his opinion on
aquí a opinar de
gossip, I mean, I think that I think it
salseo o sea yo creo que yo creo que
depends on the topics no
depende de los temas no
but
pero
apart from that he will get along with Dallas but the thing
aparte delo se llevará con Dallas pero
is that
es que la
[Music]
[Música]
people this for example is a bit of a
gente esto por ejemplo es un poco
bully attitude no this for example eh It's not
actitud bully no esto por ejemplo eh No
a bit of a bully attitude Wanting what you
es un poco actitud bully El querer queas
do to him in the void I mean people
le haga en el vacío O sea la gente
want and with me the same I don't know if now it
quiere y conmigo igual no sé si ahora
will be when he mentions me not that he
será cuando me menciona no que que me
stops talking to me with the dx and it's like let's
deje de hablar con el dx y es como
see if he hasn't done anything to me when he
a ver si a mí no me ha hecho nada cuando
does something to me then we won't see them anymore No
me haga algo pues ya no las veremos No
if he does something to me we won't see them anymore
si me hace algo ya no las veremos
[Music]
[Música]
eh For example, for me last night Vin
eh Por ejemplo para mí anoche vin me
did something to me that I don't want to know anything about
hizo algo que yo no quiero saber nada de
her, I'll tell you now  Here I don't care, I'm
ella ya ya os lo digo Aquí me da igual
not going to go into detail but I'm
no voy a entrar en detalle pero estoy
very pissed off I'm very pissed off and we
muy [__] estoy muy [__] y nos
have stopped
hemos dejado de
following each other but absolute disappointment okay
seguir pero decepción absoluta vale
let's go I don't care I'm going to talk the same
vamos me da igual voy a hablar lo mismo
about her whether she talks to me or not eh eh I'm going to
de ella me hable o no me hable eh eh voy
say what I have to say whether he's a villain
decir lo que tenga que decir sea villin
or the pope you understand but with Dallas
sea el papa me entiendes pero con Dallas
the same Let's see if I have a cordial relationship
lo mismo A ver sí tengo una cordialidad
with him he's a colleague here from YouTube just
con él es un colega de aquí de YouTube
like Dallas well maybe I've
igual que el Dallas bueno a lo mejor lo
known him for longer no but in the end
conozco de más tiempo no pero al final
I'm not in his it's that I don't even know him
yo no estoy en su es que no lo conozco
in person I'm not at his house I
ni en persona yo no estoy en su casa no
'm not in his in his videos we don't collaborate
estoy en su en sus vídeos no colaboramos
every week I mean no no it's not I don't
todas las semanas o sea no no es no
have the relationship with Dallas that I have
tengo la relación con Dallas que tengo
with Alanne or with Elena for example you
con alanne o con Elena por ejemplo
understand me I don't have I don't have
entiendes Me entiendes no tengo no tengo
that relationship I have a very
esa relación tengo una relación bien
good relationship we get along sometimes
buena nos llevamos bien algunas veces
we agree there are others in which we do
Estamos de acuerdo hay otras en las que
n't I mean how many times from here have I said no
no O sea Cuántas veces de aquí he dicho
in many things we have not agreed
no en muchas cosas no hemos coincidido
but it's like no no it's not that you hang out with
pero es como no no es que te juntas con
Dallas it's that you have to get out you have to
Dallas es que tienes que sacar tienes
get away from the world of Dallas and like
que alejarte del mundo de Dallas y como
In what world of Dallas now Turbo pl a
En qué mundo de Dallas ahora Turbo pl un
video  defending vin
video defendiendo a vin
eh I don't know the truth I don't know I don't know no
eh No lo sé la verdad no lo sé No lo sé
no I'm not going to say anything at the moment
no no yo no voy a contar nada de momento
but for me it was too much for me I didn't like
pero para mí se pasó para mí no me gustó
the truth what happened yesterday I didn't like it at all I'm not
la verdad lo de ayer no me gustó nada no
going to go into it I understand his thing well I understand you
voy a entrar entiendo su movida bueno
know
entiendo sabes
but well what I was going with that was
pero bueno a lo que iba con eso que era
an internet colleague I mean not friends I did
una colega de internet o sea no amigos
n't think we're friends let's see friends
No pensé que somos amigos a ver amigos
friend for me Hi lanne Elena okay the
amiga para mi Hi lanne Elena vale la
people that I met in person that we
gente que que conocio en persona que
talk to every day that ask me
hablamos todos los días que me preguntan
about my children that I don't know what but you're
por mis hijos que no sé qué pero tú eres
a person with whom I get along
una persona con la que me llevo bien de
little more from here you understand me I mean and
aquí poco más me entiendes o sea y el
Tas Well yes we have told each other our
Tas Pues sí nos hemos contado nuestras
little things we have had moments in which
cosillas hemos tenido momentos en los
we have had more relationship less
que hemos tenido más relación menos
relationship but he is not a person with
relación pero no es una persona con la
whom
que
I drown my sorrows right now the
yo ahogue mis penas ahora mismo la
truth is there is a cordiality he hasn't
verdad se hay una cordialidad él no se
messed with me I have no reason to
ha metido conmigo Yo no lo tengo por qué
attack him Now when I disagree
atacar Ahora cuando estoy en desacuerdo
Well I say it what do you want me to
Pues yo que lo digo qué quieres que te
tell you do you understand but it's like here the
diga me entiendes pero es como aquí el
delox that is what I was going for the
delox que es a lo que iba el
delox the delo B  hel vaa evening, that is,
delox el delo B hel vaa velada o sea el
delos goes to the evening, delos talks
delos va a la velada el delos se habla
to Ricky, talks to Agustín, talks
con Ricky se habla con Agustín se habla
to tokis, who doesn't get along with Dallas,
con tokis que no se lleva con el Dallas
where is delox hidden? What should we
dónde está metido el delox Qué hay que
not talk to Dallas? Hey, if I get along, is
no hablarle a Dallas Oye si yo me llevo
n't he a tremendous crybaby? Everyone already
no es tremendo llorón ya todo el mundo
has a very bad image of del.
tiene una muy mala imagen de del a día
Today, the vast majority of people, I
de hoy la gran mayoría de gente yo le
warned him, we warned him because delox was
avisé yo lo avisamos porque delox era
a person close to us, not a
una persona cercana a nosotros no
close friend, but close because
cercana de amigo pero cercana de que
we are in Andorra and from time to time we
estamos en andorra y de vez en cuando
coincide and stanix worked for him
coincidimos y stanix trabajaba para él y
and we warned him, we said, man, you have to
y le avisamos le dijimos tío has de
maintain your objectivity, you have to stop
mantener tu objetividad has de dejar de
hanging around with Dallas, you have to do your
moverte con Dallas has de hacer tu
podcast and no, no, no, no, let's
podcast y que no que no que no que
condemn
condenemos a
kcu, that Dallas in the podcast, that we
kcu que Dallas en el podcast que que
condemn cocu, that is, here at the millor,
condenemos a cocu o sea aquí al millor
what seems terrible to him is that we
lo que le parece fatal es que que
condemn czu, what does he think is
condenemos a czu qué es lo que le parece
wrong? Dallas has gone to the little once and then
mal Dalas ha ido al poca una vez y luego
a
un
debate, no, no, let's condemn Claro
debate no no que condenemos a Claro
because it is that according to  the best one shouldn't
porque es que según el millor no hay que
condemn ccu because it's
condenar a ccu porque es una
nonsense according to the best one,
ronada según el millor no hay que
kocu shouldn't be condemned Well in fact the best one is
condenar a kocu Bueno de hecho el millor
going to suck up to cocu, the one
va a hacerle la pelota al cocu al de
from the evening went up to accompany him, I
esto de la velada se subió a acompañarlo
think it was, he didn't go up to suck up to him,
creo que fue no se subió a hacerle la
no, and then ccu gave him his
pelotilla no y luego ccu le dio su
recognition, I mean, he's got balls the
reconocimiento o sea tiene huevos el
best one, you have balls to tell
millor tienes huevos tú para decirle a
anyone who to hang out with And who not to
nadie con quién juntarse Y con quién no
when you're defending the ccu and you go
cuando estás defendiendo al ccu y te vas
to the evening to suck up to czu, man I
a la velada hacerle la pelota al czu tío
mean, you must have balls eh I mean, he must have
O sea tienes que tener huevazos
balls
eh o sea tiene que tener huevazos
eh No, no, what's hurting you Is that you have an
eh No no lo lo que te perjudica Es que
opinion on the controversies in Dallas and I don't
opines de las polémicas de Dallas y no
know what but no, no, the thing with kocu, he took
sé qué pero no no lo de con kocu me ha
a picture of me and also he asked
una fotito y además se la pide él eh a
him to suck the ccu's balls
él a comerle los huevos al ccu
eh I don't know how many that or that's it, I can go [ __ ] myself like
eh No sé cuántos que o ya está puedo a
delux, there are
tomar por culo en plan delux de quedan
four news broadcasts left at this rate, you know
cuatro telediarios a este ritmo sabes Ya
I'm not even able to go back, you know,
no soy ni siquiera s puede volver atrás
now he's with Javi oliveira, already, already
sabes ahora está con Javi oliveira ya ya
in  the plan is that they are cancers like
en plan es que son cánceres en plan
Dallas and Javi Oliveira are cancers and
Dallas y el Javi oliveira son cánceres y
everyone who is
todo el mundo que somos
cancer thinks they are cancers except for a few
cánceres opina que son cánceres menos
people I don't know how he came to
cuatro gatos yo no sé cómo ha llegado a
the conclusion that hanging around with those
la conclusión de que moverse con esa
people is going to add anything to him
gente le va a sumar algo siendo
realistically stanix le Carr read a
realistas stanix le Carr leó un podcast
brutal podcast stanix managed to get a
brutal stanix consiguió que tuviera un
top two podcast in Spain and he you are really
podcast top dos en España y el tú eres
stupid the best I mean at what point does
tontísimo el millor o sea en qué momento
the editor take control of your channel
te carrilea el canal el
but man do you think these things or does it
editor pero tío tú piensas estas cosas o
happen to you like when you saw a policeman and
te pasa como cuando viste a un policía y
you started uploading stories on
te pusiste a subir historias en
instagram insulting the
instagram insultando a la policía de
Andorran police and you had to delete them because
andorra y las tuviste que borrar porque
otherwise they would kick you out of
si no te echaban de
Andorra man you almost lost your channel
andorra tío que casi te quedas sin canal
and your livelihood because you spent
y sin medio de vida porque te pusiste
half an hour insulting your ex in
durante media hora a insultar a tu ex de
the worst ways who the [ __ ] are you that you
las peores formas quién [__] eres tú Que
support koku to tell no one
apoyas a koku para decirle a nadie que
not to hang out with Dallas
no se junte con el Dallas
man your channel was hanging by a
tío que tu canal estuvo pendiente de un
thread because he insulted cristinini man you have to
hilo porque insultaba a cristinini tío
kiss where she steps
que tienes que besar por donde pise
cristinini for not having wanted to
cristinini de no haberte querido
report you How  [ __ ] you're going to say the
denunciar Cómo [__] vas a decir la
[ __ ] idiot
[__]
[ __ ] that the channel is being
gilipollez de que el canal se lo
screwed by the editor
carrilea el editor
the guest is being screwed No no the
se lo carrilear el invitado No no el
editor son of a [ __ ]
editor hijo mío
creature that your peak viewers is
criatura que tu pico de espectadores es
having Dallas in your live and
haber tenido al Dallas en tu directo y
you quiet in a corner what the [ __ ] are you
tú callado en una esquina qué [__] me
telling me I mean how are you going to have
estás contando o sea cómo vas a tener
the [ __ ] balls How are you going to have the
los [__] huevos Cómo vas a tener los
[ __ ] balls to start saying No no it's that
[__] huevos de ponerte a decir No no es
delox is doing bad because he's with
que a delox le va mal porque junta con
Javi and Dallas dude your
el Javi y con el Dallas tío que tu
most watched live of your entire [ __ ] life
directo más visto de toda tu [__] vida
your most watched live of your life is
que tu directo más visto de tu vida es
you in a corner While Dallas
tú en una esquina Mientras que el Dallas
was fighting with someone else and you're not contributing
se peleaba con otro y tú no aportando
absolutely anything because you're not even worth being a
absolutamente nada porque es que ni para
moderator
moderador
okay How are you going to have the balls
vales vale Cómo vas a tener los huevos
to say that dasas is hurting you in
de decir que el dasas te perjudica en
numbers when literally your peak
números cuando literal tu pic de
viewers of your entire career as a
espectadores de toda tu carrerita de
LOL player
jugador de LOL
is Dallas in your live come on come on you have to
es el Dallas en tu
do it come on he's just squandered it it's
hacer vamos solo lo ha dilapidado es
impressive and look at that he squandered it by
impresionante y mira que encima lo ha
warning him eh we told him
dilapidado avisándole eh que le dijimos
don't do this don't do this  don't do
no hagas esto no hagas esto no hagas
this don't do this patapam well that's it
esto no hagas esto patapam pues ya está
and the top one the top one is The Wild
y el top un el top uno es The Wild
project I don't even believe it's in Top they're not there it's
project Ya no creo ni que esté en Top no
just cancer of gossip in the
están solo hace cáncer de salseo en los
podcasts I can't do it
podcast yo no
dude really the best you're
puedo tío de verdad el millor eres más
shorter than the sleeves of
corto que las mangas del chaleco de
Jordi's vest Wild project that you just
Jordi Wild project que acabas de
mentioned I mean the literal peak the peak
mencionar o sea el pico literal el pico
of without fear of success literally is
de sin miedo al éxito literalmente es
gossip I mean the first episodes that
salseo o sea los primeros episodios que
had views of the [ __ ]
tuvieron visitas del del del [__]
podcast are
podcast son
gossip without more okay when it has less
salseo sin más vale cuando tiene menos
views is when there is no salt
visita es cuando no hay sal
And it's not just gossip okay it's not
Y es que no hace solo salseo vale es que
just gossip it's not a
no hace solo salseo no es un podcast de
gossip podcast look at super gifted with aspergism those
salseo mira superdotado con asperge los
two who think the earth is
dos estos que se creen que la tierra es
flat worth it miso I mean the m espirito
plana vale el miso o sea el m espirito
Poker René valentí bro Antonio the
Poker René valentí bror Antonio el de
fat one half million views the
los gordos medio millón de visita el
other andoni the one who shoots up or doesn't shoot up
otro andoni el que se chuta o no se
be this guy not even
sea este tío ni siquiera
through his head when he's going to speak dude I
por su cabeza cuando va a hablar tío o
mean the normal thing with the human body is that
sea lo normal del cuerpo humano es que
when you're going to say something you pass it through you don't
tú cuando vas a decir algo lo pasas no
pass it through your brain  you process it and
lo pasas por tu cerebro lo procesas y
then you let it out of your mouth I
luego lo sueltas por la boca Yo a lo
might not sound a little good but at
mejor vocalizo un poco mal pero por lo
least I've thought about what I'm going to say No
menos he pensado lo que voy a decir No
but let the guy with all his balls
pero sea el tío con todos sus huevos se
start saying No no it's not like now you
pone a decir No no es que ahora
only do gossip in the podcast Before
solamente haces salseo en el podca antes
you were doing better and now you're doing worse because
Te iba mejor y ahora te va peor porque
now you only do
ahora solo haces
gossip man What are they
salseo tío Cuáles son Espérate que me
Wait until I find out What are the episodes for which
entere yo Cuáles son los epios por los
the podcast was known because if
que el podcast fue conocido porque si no
I'm not mistaken if I'm not mistaken the podcast
me equivoco si no me equivoco el podcast
became known for bringing
se hizo conocido por llevar a
Dallas the moror like gossip It's when you
Dallas el moror like salseo Es cuando te
hang out with Dallas but he doesn't
juntas con Dallas pero es que ni
even process what he said I mean
siquiera procesa lo que ha dicho o sea
what he just said he hasn't even
lo que acaba de decir ni siquiera lo ha
said it he screwed up out of his mouth okay I mean
dicho lo ha cagado por por la boca vale
how is it that the podcast used to
o sea cómo que el podc antes
be the worthy successor of project and now it's
era el digno sucesor de project y ahora
not going going going downhill because it's been
ya no es va va va a cuesta abajo porque
gossip yes literally the little one and
ha se salseo si literalmente el poca y
for hanging out with Dallas yes literally
por juntarse con Dallas si literalmente
the posca they met him for hanging out with
el posca lo conocieron por juntarse con
Dallas literally the posca they
Dallas literalmente el posca lo
met him and he met for hanging out with
conocieron y se conoció por juntarse con
Dallas
Dallas
literal
literal
literal and when the podcast has more
literal y cuando el podcast tiene más
visits when it's
visitas cuando es de
gossip, just goes with what he said It's that
salseo sin más va lo que ha dicho Es que
the best is always a liar, I
es que el millor es mentiroso siempre o
mean, the word of the best is worth
sea la palabra del millor no vale
absolutely nothing, dude,
absolutamente nada tío nunca
absolutely nothing is ever worth what the
absolutamente nada vale lo que diga el
best says, okay It's not that he literally does the
millor vale No es que literal hace el
gossip, the best, the best, you start
salseo el millor el millor te pones a
sucking Dallas's dick because you want him to
chuparle el [__] a Dallas porque quieres
let you react to his videos, dude,
que te deje reaccionar a sus vídeos tío
you created a kik account so you
que te has creado una cuenta en kik para
can react to
poder reaccionar a los vídeos de
Dallas' videos because you start throwing [ __ ]
Dallas porque te pones a tirarle [__]
at Dallas, you go run, you get angry, I
a Dallas te vas vas corriendo a enfadar
mean, I'm going to make a video for you this week,
o sea voy a hacerte un vídeo esta semana
the best, I'm going to make a video for you, you
el millor voy a hacerte un vídeo ya me
've really pissed me off, I'm going to make a
has tocado los [__] voy a hacerte un
video for you, dude, I'm going to make a
vídeo tío voy a hacerte una saga de
video saga for you, you deserve it, dude, because
vídeo que te mereces tío porque es que
you deserve it because I have so many
te la mereces porque es que tengo tantas
things to say about you, dude, that I can't
cosas de decir sobre ti tío que no me
fit in here in an excerpt, but I'm going
cabe aquí en un extracto pero es que voy
to make a video for you, dude, I mean, you were sucking up
a hacerte un vídeo tío o sea le hacías
to Dallas and
la pelota al Dallas y
you thought that this cover was Rosa Okay,
opinabas que esta carátula era Rosa Vale
and literally when Dallas made the
y literal cuando el Dallas le hizo el
video for by, you started
vídeo a by te
defending  ibai of what ibai
a hac a defender a ibai de lo que ibai
never asked you to defend him okay And
nunca te pidió que lo defendieras vale Y
suddenly the cover was yellow
ya de repente la carátula eraa amarilla
and literally the same thing that you said that
y literalmente en lo mismo que decías
the same cover was Pink it was
que la misma carátula era Rosa era
yellow because you were angry with
amarilla porque te habías enfadado con
Tas and then after saying that the
el Tas y luego después de decir que la
cover was yellow and insulting insult insult
carátula era amarilla y de insultar
insult Dallas you
insultar insultar insultar a Dallas te
started saying that Dallas should be
pusiste a decir que al Dallas había que
left without a job that he should be
dejarlo sin trabajo que debería estar
banned from all platforms okay And
baneado de todas las plataformas vale Y
after saying this after saying
después de decir esto después de decir
that that he has to be left without a job
eso que se tiene que quedar sin trabajo
that I know they have to ban him from all
que se que lo tienen que banear de todas
platforms then you took your
las plataformas después cogiste tus
balls your balls you put them in a
huevos tus huevos los subiste en un
cart okay in one of these
carrito vale en un carrito de estos de
shopping carts there with really
la compra ahí con las ruedas bien
big wheels so it can handle the weight of
grandes para que pueda con el peso de
your balls okay And you went like a
tus [__] vale Y te fuiste como un
Lamb and I have it and I have it okay And if they give
Cordero y lo tengo y lo tengo vale Y si
me permission I'll put it well I'm not going
me dan permiso lo pongo bueno no lo voy
to put it I'll describe it people are going to
a poner lo describo la gente me va a
believe me because you don't have words like a
creer porque tú no tienes palabr como un
Lamb you went to tell him please
Cordero te fuiste a decirle por favor me
let me react to your videos
dejas que reacciones a tus vídeos en
live literally that's what you
directo literal eso
did literally that's what  you did
hiciste literal eso es lo que hiciste
Who is the cancer Dallas Javi That
Quién es el cáncer el Dallas el Javi Ese
is the cancer or you that Dallas told you
es el cáncer o tú que el Dallas te dijo
no and and you created a twit account
no y y te creaste una cuenta de twit
to be able to profit from
para poder lucrar del contenido de
Dallas' content and then he started to cry because
Dallas y luego se puso a llorar porque
when he got banned from Twitch because he
cuando le banearon de Twitch porque se
spent half an hour insulting his
pegó durante media hora insultando a su
ex something that Dallas has never done
ex cosa que el Dallas no ha hecho
okay they banned him With good reason
nunca vale le banearon Con justa razón
because he spent half an hour insulting
porque se pegó media hora insultando a
Cristinini saying that the only
cristinini diciendo que por el único
reason he wasn't at McDonald's was
motivo que no estaba en el macdona era
tatata okay [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] imbecile
tatata vale [__] subnormal [__] imbécil
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] to his ex
[__] subnormal [__] [__] a su ex
okay And then the poor little creature the
vale Y luego el pobre criaturita la
poor little creature sat down he felt really
pobre criaturita se sentó se sintió muy
sold out because Dallas was sending him
vendido porque el Dallas le mandaba
messages telling him haha ​​that he sent them to you for
mensajes diciéndole jaj que te los mandó
four days and you started saying that you that he
cuatro días y te pusiste a decir que te
sent them to you his whole life dude this
que te los mandaba toda la vida tío este
guy Or do more you know four times that it
tío O hacer más sabes cuatro veces que
coincided at my house that I was recording a
coincidió en mi casa que estaba grabando
podcast at my house all four times I
podcast en mi casa las cuatro veces le
told him enough Dallas enough Dallas
dije basta de Dallas basta de Dallas
enough Dallas enough with giving your opinion
basta de Dallas basta de dar tu opinión
and taking a stand  in favor of but dude
y de posicionarte a favor de pero tío
then you're sick with Dallas
pues entonces estás malito con el dalla
like four times a person comes to your
o sea cuatro veces va una persona a tu
house and instead of talking about what you
casa y tú en vez de hablar de lo que tú
have to offer you talk about Dallas I
tengas para ofrecer ablas del Dallas O
mean imagine you go to a streamer's house
sea imagínate que tú vas a la casa de un
and he comes to tell you right in your
streamer y te viene a decir por toda la
[ __ ] face enough with Dallas enough with
[__] cara basta de Dallas basta de
Dallas enough with Dallas when your
Dallas basta de Dallas cuando a ti tu
mom lets you talk about Dallas okay your
madre te deja hablar de Dallas vale tu
mom and dad give you permission to
madre y tu padre te dan permiso para que
talk about Dallas but this guy goes and you
tú hables de Dallas pero este chico va y
go to his house and he says enough with
vas a su casa y te dice basta de
Dallas But what the [ __ ]
Dallas Pero esto qué [__]
is this But what the
es
[ __ ] is this enough with this
Pero esto qué [__]
condemnation coscu enough with
esas basta de condena coscu basta de
doing enough with this condemnation c but come on this
hacer basta de condena c pero vamos esto
is already a joke I mean this guy this guy B
ya es de traca o sea este tío este tío B
enough with this condemnation cocu
basta de condena cocu te
tells you but dude what has Dallas done to you he
dice pero tío que te ha hecho el Dallas
showed you the
te ha enseñado el
blunderbuss for you to be so traumatized
trabuco para que te quedes tan traumado
podcast where you give your [ __ ] opinion
podcast donde das tu [__] opinión
interview with the guy Make objective
entrevista al tío Haz podcast objetivos
and neutral podcasts but apart from that look at you he
y neutal pero es que aparte fíjate tú
's bringing Dallas into
que es que está metiendo a Dallas en una
something that has nothing to do with it because it doesn't
cosa que ni tiene que ver porque es que
even have anything to do with it here  come
ni siquiera ni siquiera aquí tiene nada
on with this controversy
que ver delo con esta polémica
dude I mean not even Dallas has to do
tío o sea ni siquiera el Dallas tiene
with this controversy he's
que ver con esta polémica le está
saying one thing to uncle sh And he says Well
diciendo una cosa al tío sh Y dice Bueno
just like delox who has to
pues igual que delox que se tiene que
stop hanging out with Dallas because you
dejar de juntar con Dallas porque tú lo
say so because you say so Of course
digas porque tú lo digas Claro que sí
man
hombre
Today is the day delox your podcast will be Well
Hoy es el día delox tu podcast erá Bueno
but Dallas but Dallas trales and you're going to do
pero Dalas pero Dalas trales y te va a
well because you're having a good
ir bien porque estás teniendo una buena
formula good guests he did what he
fórmula buenos invitados hizo lo que le
wanted because you're having
salió de la poll porque estás teniendo
a good formula good guests dude
una buena fórmula buenos invitados tío
the best really I mean stop [ __ ] up
el millor de verdad O sea deja de [__]
what you say and think before you say it I
lo que dices y piénsalo antes de sarlo O
mean you have a good formula you're
sea tienes una buena fórmula estás
having good guests literally
teniendo buenos invitados literalmente
Ricky Eddie the most relevant thing about his
Ricky Eddie lo más relevante de su
podcast what he talks about Dallas
podcast lo que habla de Dallas
literally the first known podcast of
literalmente primer podcast conocido de
fearless the success Dallas is
sin miedo el éxito Dallas vale
literally worth your [ __ ] podcast dude the most
literalmente tu [__] podcast tío lo más
relevant was that you talked about
relevante fue que hablaste de
Dallas literally the second most
Dallas literalmente lo segundo más
relevant thing about fearless and success or what has
relevante de sin miedo y éxito o lo que
been the most the debate of Dallas with
más ha sido el debate de Dallas con
nimu is that well and what Willy re which
nimu es que bueno y lo de Willy re que
is another separate topic look that
es otro tema aparte que mira ese no
has nothing to do with Dallas but the
tiene nada que ver con Dallas pero lo
rest I
demás
mean windy was also very relevant and
o sea windy también fue muy relevante y
de windy was a steak with Juan and with Ari
lo de windy fue bifeo con Juan y con Ari
you know what the best guy is saying is
sabes que lo que está diciendo el millor
simply and genuinely a
sencilla y genuinamente es
lie it's that literally what
mentira es que literalmente lo que está
the best guy is saying is genuinely false
diciendo el millor es genuinamente falso
dude he's
tío es que está
lying out of ego
mintiendo por ego
and he's going to crash it's going to crash 100% 100%
y se va a estampar se estampar 100% 100%
I would risk both hands it's going to
me jugaría las dos manos se va a
crash it's what there is it still has
estampar es lo que hay sigue teniendo
good views on YouTube things have
buenas views en YouTube las cosas tienen
a limited life like it's going to
una vida limitada en plan se va a
crash but I don't know you have stanix and you
estampar pero no sé tienes a stanix y me
have me who are two of the
tienes a mí que somos dos de las
people who understand the internet the most in
personas que más entiende de internet de
Spain and we literally tell you how to
España y literalmente te decimos Cómo
do things and you don't listen to us Ho
hacer las cosas y no nos haces caso Ho
[ __ ] dude the best guy you literally have
shit tío el millor literalmente tienes
20,000 views on each video you
20.000 visitas en cada vídeo
literally have 20,000 views on
literalmente tienes 20.000 visitas en
each video
cada vídeo
dude he literally came to ixter who has been around for
tío literalmente ha lgado en ixter que
2 years and has the same number of
lleva 2 años y tien los mismos
viewers as you on Twitch
espectadores que tú en Twitch
wake up wake up what the [ __ ] are you
espabila espabila qué [__] me estás
talking to me about following your
hablando de que hay que seguir tu
advice what is your advice insulting your
consejo cuál es tu consejo insultar a tu
ex to get banned almost indefinitely
ex para que te baneen casi indefinido
What is the  [ __ ] advice that you should
Cuál es el [__] consejo que hay que
follow
seguir
yours is stratospheric virgin Holy
tuyo es uno estratosférico virgen Santa
Thank goodness you're a humble guy
Menos mal que tú eres un tipo humilde la
humility is a pretty
humildad es una característica bastante
negative characteristic if you think you're good you
negativa si tú crees que eres bueno
can just share it I'm not going to
puedes simplemente compartirlo no voy a
say that I'm not good at what I'm
decir que no se me da bien lo que se me
good at you haven't run a
da bien llevas sin hacer funcionar un
YouTube channel in 5 years every time I've
canal de YouTube 5 años cada vez que
touched a YouTube channel it has worked
tocado un canal de YouTube ha funcionado
every time try hard League of
cada vez try hard canal de League of
Legends channel number one in League of Legends
Legends número uno de League of Legends
Spain try hard the channel of the double chin
España try hard el canal de la papada
Army half a million views on each [ __ ]
Army medio millón de visitas cada [__]
YouTube video of the double chin Army every
vídeo de YouTube de la papada Army cada
time I do something it always works there's
vez que hago algo funciona siempre hay
only one thing The guy puts millor in
solo una cosa El tío se pone millor en
the name and they ask him for humility there's only
el nombre y le piden humildad hay solo
one thing that can fail me and that's
una cosa que me puede fallar y es la
consistency and it's not my fault it's
constancia y no es por mi culpa es por
because of surrounding myself with incompetents many
por rodearme de incompetentes muchas
times I'm 1% sure that I could make
veces estoy 1% seguro que podría hacer
a YouTube channel about Lili it was your
un canal de YouTube sobrea Lili era tu
Twitter the one who was watching
Twitter el que estaba viendo cualquier
anything and it would blow it up but it would blow it up like the
cosa y lo petara pero lo petara en plan
top 3 in Spain top 2 in Spain in
top 3 de España top 2 de España en
less than half a year 100%
cuestión de menos de medio año 100%
would make it work  any
haría funcionar cualquier canal de
YouTube channel cu Well let's see if you can
YouTube cu Pues a ver si hace funcionar
at least make yours work Well let's see if you can
por lo menos el tuyo pues a ver si hace
at least make yours work because neither
funcionar por lo menos el tuyo porque ni
Sas has a clue anymore eh I mean
Sas techa la pata ya eh o sea
literally he hasn't even put his foot in it anymore
literalmente ni le ha echado la pata ya
YouTube would make it
cara de Youtube de cualquier cosa lo
work for anything Why would I do it Why do I
haría funcionar para qué voy a hacerlo
want more Do it for what For
para qué quiero más Hazlo de qué para
what To make more money if I'm not
qué Para hacer más dinero si ya no me lo
going to be able to spend it anymore it doesn't make any
voy a poder gastar no tiene ningún
sense I do what I want I make a
sentido hago lo que me apetece hago
League of Legends channel because I
canal de League of Legends porque me
want to not because I think I'm going to
apetece no porque crea que voy a
break the internet by making a
reventar internet haciendo un canal de
League of Legends channel because I want to
League of Legends porque me apetece
have a cool League of
tener un canal chulo de League of
Legends channel I want to Have a [ __ ] cool
Legends me apetece Ten un [__] canal
League of Legends channel constantly That's it I do
chulo de League of Legends constante Ya
n't want to get rich I'm not going to
está no quiero hacerme rico no voy a
earn a single euro with the YouTube channel
ganar ni un euro con el canal de YouTube
but I want you to have
pero me apetece que tengáis contenido
cool League of Legends content And yeah and I
guapo de League of Legends Y ya y me
want that when Twitch explodes I
apetece que cuando Twitch explote que yo
can go to YouTube to stream
me pueda ir a YouTube a hacer Stream
because I have a cool channel there are
porque tenga un canal chulo ahí son esas
things like that I think there's not much more
cosas las que pienso no hay mucho más
So you consider yourself better than Mr
Entonces te consideras mejor que Mr
beast  eh [ __ ] or what one thing is to
beast eh [__] o qué una cosa es
say that I can run
decir que puedo hacer funcionar
any YouTube channel on
cualquier canal de YouTube sobre
any topic and then
cualquier temática y luego que me
consider myself better than the best in
considere mejor que el mejor de la
history man What a character man, I don't know
historia tío Qué personaje tío yo no sé
if he literally thinks these things,
si estas cosas él literalmente las
I think he doesn't think what he says, I think he
piensa yo creo que no piensa lo que dice
screws up what he says, that's
yo creo que lo caga lo que dice o sea
clear eh I think he doesn't think, no, he does
así de claro eh yo creo que él no piensa
n't process what he says look,
no no procesa lo que dice mira
mainly what he says is a
principalmente es que lo que dice es
lie, I mean, what he has said about
mentira o sea lo que ha dicho sobre
many topics is a lie, so there we
muchos temas es mentira entonces ahí ya
could get into a debate, what he
podríamos entrar en un debate lo que
says is a lie
dice es mentira
because he remembers it wrong or he's lying on
porque lo recuerda mal o miente a
purpose, he misinterprets things,
propósito interpreta mal las cosas le
LoL, his mind is cooked, he has it cooked, he
tiene LoL la mente comida se la tiene
lies on purpose or he lies because he has
miente a propósito o miente porque tiene
another concept because of course there are
otro concepto porque claro aquí hay
many options here, there are no
muchas opciones no
please tell me what, tell me that Uncle
hay por favor Dime que dime que el tío
Sur has papped him tell me that Uncle Sur
Sur lo ha papeado dime que el tío Sur lo
has papped him
ha papeado por
please I trust you eh Uncle Sur if not I'm
favor confío en ti eh tío Sur si no te
going to demand you again that you
voy a exigir otra vez que pidas
apologize for the opinion let's see, I'm going to watch
perdón la opinión a ver voy a ver
the clip first, what clip do you share Electra
primero el clip qué clip comparte
Electra you are becoming
Electra Electra te estás haciendo cada
more famous every day, aunt Give me some fame
día más famosa tía Dame algo de fama
please let's see  This is what the coolest guy who
porfa a ver esto le dijo el millor que
was commenting on the clip about bullying and
estuvo comentando el clip del bullying y
autism told him. I'm 100% sure that they did it to the
el autismo Estoy 100% seguro que a los
four of them at school. I'd bet
cuatro les hacían en el cole apostaría
a lot, I'd bet hard
mucho apostaría fuerte a
that he's completely sure. He
que ya está está completamente seguro Él
was at that school, man, the coolest. If you
estaba en ese colegio tío el millor si
're not even sure about the [ __ ]
no estás seguro ni de las [__]
conversations you have with me, man, you
conversaciones que tienes tú conas tío
tell whatever you want, how are you
que cuentas lo que te da la gana cómo
going to know what they did to Uncle Shur
vas a saber lo que le hacían al tío shur
in Argentina at his school if you don't
en Argentina en su colegio si no sabes
even know what they did to you on the internet.
ni lo que te hacían a ti en internet
Man, few of them ate sandwiches, none of
tío pocos bocadillo se comían ninguno de
these four, few eh, few
de estos cuatro pocos eh pocos
sandwiches were eaten in the
bocadillos se comían en el patio del
schoolyard, gone to the bathroom, and when I got into it, a
cole ido al baño y cuando ent la una
fistfight, he had glasses and everything, he bled,
piña cl tenía lentes y todo Lía sangre
suspensions, we all laughed. I still
suspensiones todos camos risa Sigo
think the same thing I've defended other
pensando lo mismo que defendido otras
times, that you have to learn what your
veces que has de aprender cuál es tu
place is, okay, Uncle Shur, what he does well is
lugar vale tío shur lo que hace bien es
neutrality, don't give his opinion, expose eh,
neutralidad no dar su opinión exponer eh
the toilets of the day, people like him,
los aseos del día la gente le cae bien
he likes what he does, keep the formula. You
le gusta lo que hace mantén la fórmula
don't have to want more, you're
No tienes por qué querer más estás
having a lot of visits, you're having
teniendo muchas visitas estás teniendo
money, he must be billing well, Uncle
dinero debe estar facturando bien tío
Shur, per month  that's it, don't want any more, nobody
shur al mes ya está no quieras más nadie
wants to see what Uncle Shur has to
quiere ver lo que El tío shur tiene que
say about something bi The same thing happens with the
decir sobre algo bí Igual pasa con los
others, the other three people, you know,
otros las otras tres personas sabes
you have to understand what you can, the
tienes que entender qué es lo que puedes
other three
las otras tres
people, not even Gibel is not into gossip, man, how the hell are you going to say that the same thing happens with the other three people, how are you going to say literally, Tommy's channel
personas Cómo vas a decir literalmente
is a compilation in which
el canal de Tommy es una recopilación en
he gives his opinion on
la que él pone su opinión respecto a
characters that were relevant in the world of YouTube, the one with the stutterer,
personajes que eran relevantes en el
the stutterer is a little, no, yeah, well, a little like the
Bueno un poco así como la salsería y tal
salsería and such, no, but it's that Guibel's It's that Guibel's
En qué eres mejor que el resto y no
is into anime and reacts to anything,
que el resto debel pues pues gibel está
how are you going to say it's not the
vida del señor en qué va a ser gibel
same as the others, man, no ...
mejor que
What does gibel do better
algo por el estilo Qué hace gibel mejor
than anyone else? How is gibel going to
que nadie en qu en qué gibel va a
learn that he's better than the rest, the
aprender que es mejor que el resto el
poor thing, if he has too much to do with talking
pobrecito si demasiado tiene con hablar
and not [ __ ] himself on things you're
y no cagarse a la vez en cosas en las
not good at, the one who spoke is whose
que no se te da bien habló el que su
moderately strong point is playing
punto medianamente fuerte es jugar al
LoL and he spends all day giving his opinion on everything
LoL y está todo el día opinando de todo
getting into [ __ ] and [ __ ] it up, not even
metiéndose en [__] y cagándola
haxter can beat him No, you also
ni haxter le gana No si tú también
have to understand what you can
tienes que entender que es lo que puedes
offer in that you're better than the rest and
ofrecer en que eres mejor que el resto y
not try to get into things that you're
no intentar meterte en cosas en las que
not good at yito How many times have they
no se te da bien yito Cuántas veces te
told you to focus on LoL and
han dicho que te enfoqu en el LoL y te
shut the [ __ ] up Hey, regardless of whether it's
calles la [__] boca Oye fuera de que est
true or not, but what a time to talk,
lo cierto o no pero menudo haido hablar
even if they speak totally literally,
aunque laan totalmente literalmente
literally, the moror, his most
literalmente el moror su Stream más
known Stream is
vicho es
the quiet one and Dallas on his discord
el callado y Dallas en su discord
fighting with
peleándose con
another,
otro
your most viewed Stream, no more worth it. Then
tu Stream má visto sin más vale Ya luego
you tell the others what you want, your
Tú dile lo que tú quieras a los demás tu
most viewed Stream is you, quiet and Dallas
Stream má visto es tú callado y Dallas
going live, okay, the guy tells him.
haciéndote el directo vale le dice el
Sur, moror lives in his bubble, that's why he
tío Sur moror vive en su burbuja por eso
thinks like that.  short uncle Sur has a
piensa así es cortito tío Sur tiene
lot of class stop getting into the mud with
mucha clase parar a meterse al barro con
that guy Well then I'll get involved because I do
el tipo ese Bueno pues yo me meto que yo
n't have any the moror is
no tengo ninguna el moror es
definitely a coach of
definitivamente un entrenador de
mediocre everything he says is so that
mediocres todo lo que dice es para que
the other is mediocre and he stands out
el otro sea mediocre y él sobresalga
among the mediocre
entre los mediocres
pathetic kiss Thank you very much guys
patético beso Muchas gracias chicos
nobody wants to know what the south
nadie quiere saber lo que opina el sur
says and south has trk people in their
dice y sur tiene trk personas en sus
live streams which is where they usually give their
directos que es donde suele
opinion the opinion we give is
opinar la opinión que damos es
important for the people who want to
importante para la gente que nos quiere
listen to us that we are not astrophysicists
escuchar que no somos astrofísicos
any of us and we talk about streamer gossip
ninguno y hablamos de salseo de streamer
and calm down that I farm money by giving my opinion and
y tranquilos que farmeo pasta opinando y
not giving my opinion
no opinando
take the best for your
toma el millor para tu
house there is no need for you to go with ego I like him
casa no hace falta que vayas con ego me
but if I give my point of view
cae bien pero si doy mi punto de vista
on something in which I have more idea than
sobre algo en lo que tengo más idea que
99.999999 of the people Maybe the best you
99,999999 de la gente Quizás lo mejor
can do is listen and learn
que puedes hacer es escuchar y aprender
instead of
en vez de
getting offended is what But he is
ofenderte es qué Pero esto lo está
putting this as a joke I understand
poniendo de broma entiendo
no this is what the best one who was
no esto le dijo el millor que estuvo
commenting told him he is saying this as a
comentando esto lo está diciendo de
joke
broma
no I am not saying this to you with ego but you are
no no te lo digo con ego pero estás
wrong And I'll explain it to you without drama the
errado Y te lo explico sin drama los
news is on a separate channel
noticieros están en un canal aparte
precisely for that audience and the other is
justamente para ese público y lo otro es
for the people who do care about what I
para la gente que sí le importa lo que
think or opine even so I appreciate your
pienso u opino aun así agradezco tu
advice But I assure you that I have already
consejo Pero te aseguro que ya le he
given the matter enough thought to
dado bastante más vueltas al asunto para
continue farming at full throttle zero bad vibes
seguir farmeando a tope cero mal rollo
pa it's simply my opinion about your
pa simplemente es mi opinión sobre tu
opinion you can give your opinion without
opinión puedes dar tu opinión sin
taking a position on controversial issues I still
posicionarte en temas polémicos Sigo
think that your strong point is
pensando que tu punto fuerte es la
impartiality man nobody is let's see
imparcialidad tío nadie es a ver
Impartial I think that almost all of us are
Imparcial yo creo que somos casi todos
not like biased I think that in almost
no como como parcial yo creo que en casi
all issues we are not parties we are
todos los temas no somos partes somos
impartial another thing is that you are
imparciales otra cosa es que tú seas
subjective or
subjetivo u
objective man can you tell me Some
objetivo tío me podéis decir Algún canal
gossip channel that is removing the sh news
de salseo que sea quitando el sh news
okay I understand that there is not even a
vale que entiendo que ahí no hay ni una
hint of subjectivity
pincelada de subjetividad
But what creator when he is speaking
Pero qué creador cuando está hablando
giving an
dando una
opinion is not
opinión no es subjetivo
completely subjective and that is what we all
completamente y es lo que todos nos
like to see when we watch the news
gusta ver cuando vemos los noticieros
but the thing is that when you watch the news you don't
pero es que cuando ves los noticieros no
see Uncle Sur you see what he said to
ves al tío Sur ves lo que ha dicho a
lesbi what aroya said what
lesbi lo que ha dicho aroya lo que ha
this one said  what the
dicho este lo que ha dicho el
other guy said, that every now and then you're involved
otro que cada dos por tres estés metido
in controversy for your podcast is only going to
en polémica por tu podcast solo te va a
detract from your watching, I think that the podcast thing
restar a ver yo creo que lo del podcast
can detract from it in the sense that
sí que le puede restar en el sentido de
there are very controversial things, eh, I mean,
que hay cositas muy polémicas eh o sea
very controversial like the other day, there are
muy polémicas como la del otro día hay
worse things, there are worse things of another style, there are
peores hay peores de otro estilo hay
worse things of another style. But
peores de otro estilo Pero
well, again, in my opinion, and I hope I'm
bueno de nuevo en mi opinión y ojalá me
wrong and you do very well in
equivoque y te vaya muy bien en
absolutely everything you
absolutamente todo lo que
decide, I appreciate your words. Even so, what I
decidas agradezco tus palabras aú así lo
said before, I gave my opinion before
que dije antes mi opinión la daba antes
doing the newscasts and it has never been
de hacer los noticieros y nunca ha sido
a problem, neither in numbers nor in anything,
un problema ni en números ni en nada
as long as sh news continues to provide
mientras que sh news siga dando
information as it has until today, everything will continue the
información como hasta hoy todo seguiré
same. Greetings,
igual un saludo
bro,
bro
regrettable,
lamentable
mm I'll make a video on the
mm haré un vídeo bien en el canal
main channel, I'm going to make a video about
principal voy a hacer un vídeo bien de
this, we were already underway, in
esto ya estábamos en marcha de es de
fact,
hecho
Eh, we were already underway, in
Eh ya estábamos en marcha de
had the opportunity to papele him
tuvo oportunidad de papear le
more. I don't challenge him to a debate
más Yo es que no lo reto un debate
because it's not going to work here, it's not going to work for me, he's not going to
porque aquí no va no me va no me va a
accept a debate if I didn't tell him, eh,
aceptar un debate si no se lo diría eh
if I didn't
si no se lo
explain it to him. Not for nothing, but because  I have
explicaba No por nada sino porque tengo
proof of everything I want to tell you
prueba de todo lo que les quiero decir
but the thing is that apart from that he's lying man
pero es que aparte es que miente tío
apart from that he's literally lying what he's saying isn't
aparte literalmente lo que dice no es
true not even on the subject of the subject of
verdad ni en el tema del tema de
anything absolutely nothing man of what he
nada absolutamente nada tío de lo que
says great my Ofelia who just
dice grande mi Ofelia que acaba de
gave away five more members a round of applause not
regalar cinco miembros más un aplauso no
the chat that is very stopped today the
el chat que está hoy muy paradito el
subject of members no we don't want to reach
tema miembros no no queremos llegar a
4000 what Priscila is looking at she just became a
los 4000 lo que mira Priscila se acaba
member also a kiss Priscila
de ser miembro también un beso Priscila
give everyone a lot of love to the
dle todo el mundo mucho cariño a la
people who are giving away members
gente que está regalando miembros
today
hoy
Oh
Ah
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
vale vale vale vale
okay I was still waiting to
vale vale vale vale vale me quedaba por
see this because this also goes against me I
ver esto que esto también va contra mí
think it's
creo
not that I don't want to talk much about the
no es que no quiero hablar mucho del
subject anyone because then I'll come out I'll
tema nadie porque entonces ya salgo
come out in a clip of T shur of hydra of
salgo en clip de de T shur de hidra de
such and such and such and pal you know let's see let's see but I want context I want to answer for real now eh I get up man I mean literally that I and I'm not saying it as a clown eh I mean literally yes I have to answer all the nonsense man Well actually I don't care what the
tío Bueno en realidad no me importa qué
[ __ ]
[__]
no Sara vin turns her back on jaira
no Sara vín le da la espalda a jaira
auron Play confirms new
auron Play confirma nueva
relationship
relación
plutonic honest opinion reacting to
plutonic opinión honesta reaccionando la
gubel's funa full debate the context jav
gubel debate completo el contexto jav
oliveira was too
oliveira se
special this this one We'll have to see
especial este este lo Tendremos que ver
someday eh Rich the
algún día eh los vídeos de Rich el
critic's videos I mean I'm not complaining dude what do we
crítico o sea yo no me quejo tío qué
do well some of us
hacemos pues algunos por aquí
answer here and others don't no that's it it's
contestamos y otros no no ya está es el
everyday life eh but let the gossip never die
día a día eh pero que no muera nunca el
eh I'm getting some pains
chisme eh Me están saliendo unos brascos
from carrying all the weight of the
de cargar con todo el peso del salseo
Spanish gossip look at Abi's opinion come
español ve la opinión de Abi venga
on very uncomfortable that in the end I only
vación muy incómoda que al final yo solo
comment one day a month and tomorrow I'm
comento un día al mes y es que mañana me
going to start playing bank for 7 hours and
voy a poner a jugar 7 horas al bance y
I don't give a damn eh But well in the end I
me la pela eh Pero bueno al final yo
also feel a certain way and
también me siento de una manera y me
sometimes I like to express it with you guys
gusta a veces expresarlo con vosotros
because yes Abi you tell us everything
porque que sí Abi que tú nos digas todo
and we react but you
y ya nosotros reaccionamos pero que tú
say what you want my soul don't
di lo que tú quieras mi alma no te
feel
sientas tú
cut off you also have to keep in
cortada también tenéis que tener en
mind that it's part of not feeling crazy to
cuenta que es parte de no sentirme loca
talk about these issues and that there are people
el hablar de esos temas y que haya gente
who literally see me here every
que literalmente me ve aquí todos los
day know exactly how I am know
días sabe exactamente cómoo soy sabe
exactly  what I do and tell me Hey
exactamente lo que hago y me diga Oye
Abi well no eh You don't go pushing
Abi pues no eh No vas empujando a
old women in the mataz raz while you spit
ancianas en raz mataz mientras escupes
on their heads you [ __ ] 34 people
en la cabeza te follas a 34 personas
having a boyfriend and you kill 74 streamers like you
teniendo novio y matas a 74 streamers en
know No no it's not that
sabes No no es que
scavenger
carroñero
bro I'm scared I'm also scared of
bro Tengo miedo Yo también tengo miedo a
what he's going to say to me he's going to call me
lo que me va a decir me va a decir
scavenger or something like that it's that I don't want to
carroñero o algo de eso es que no quiero
talk much about the subject nobody because it is
hablar mucho del tema nadie porque es
Then I'll come out I'll come out in a clip of of
Entonces ya salgo salgo en clip de de de
uncle shur of jav olra of such and such of which of
tío shur de jav olra de tal de cuál de
cu and of pal you know like I could Game
cu y de pal sabes en plan yo podría Game
Over Abi No man Abi for a gameover I
Over Abi No hombre Abi para un gameover
don't think he has Abi eh a thousand
tampoco creo que tenga Abi eh claras mil
things clear the best Yeah but Abi for a
cosas el millor Sí pero Abi para para un
gameover either let's see he has his I don't know the
gameover tampoco a ver tiene su no sé la
truth as much as for a gameover But
verdad tanto como para un gameover Pero
how annoying are you with a gameover I don't feel like
qué pesados sois con un gameover no
doing a gameover eh I will make
tengo ganas de hacer un gameover eh haré
videos and out but it's just useless like it doesn't matter
vídeos y fuera pero es que no sirve de
what I say it doesn't
nada en plan da igual lo que diga da
matter what I do it doesn't matter how I say it It's that it
igual lo que haga da igual como lo diga
's pointless it's because
Es que es que es pointless es porque
these people live  from this like
esta gente vive de esto en plan al igual
I make a living being an [ __ ]
que yo vivo de hacer el [__]
on camera these people make a living harassing
dentro de la cámara esa gente vive de
distorting manipulating
acosar tergiversar manipular información
third party information so that people take
de terceros para que la gente pille
sides take enemies and are
lados pille enemigos y estén
constantly involved in drama I
constantemente metidos en el drama O
mean there are people whose job is
sea hay gente que su trabajo es
literally to screw people over create
literalmente [__] a la gente crear
drama Poor thing eh of course we don't
drama Pobrecita eh claro es que no nos
make up dramas poor Abi who is
inventamos los dramas la pobre Abi que
not looking for any
es que no busca ningún
drama poor Abi who is a girl who
drama la pobre Abi que es una chica que
flies very very quickly with a super
pasa muy muy volando con el perfil super
low profile eh I mean
bajito eh o sea
Abi flies with a super low profile
Abi vuela con un perfil super bajito
calm down she doesn't mess with anyone the
tranquilita no se mete con nadie la
super discreet girl okay you have to see
muchacha super discreta vale hay que ver
that they distort things to turn
que distorsionan las cosas para ponerle
people against each other eh really be the
a la gente en contra eh ser de verdad la
[ __ ] [ __ ] and the scum of the
[__] [__] y la calaña de
internet How Wait Wait Wait I
internet Cómo Espérate Espérate Espérate
was very chill I eh Wait I
que venía muy chill yo eh Espérate que
was very chill what did she tell us So that
venía muy chill qué nos ha dicho Para
people take sides take enemies
que la gente pille lados pille enemigos
and are constantly involved in
y estén constantemente metidos en el
drama I
drama O
mean there are people whose job is
sea hay gente que su trabajo es
literally to screw people over create
literalmente [__] a la gente crear
drama
drama
m be eh Really the [ __ ] [ __ ]  [ __ ] and the
m ser eh De verdad la [__] [__] y la
scum of the internet
calaña de internet
then
entonces
Eh well
Eh bueno
great great no no wonderful I mean he called me a
genial genial no no maravilloso O sea me
stalker he
acosador me ha
called me a [ __ ] piece of [ __ ] and the biggest piece of [ __ ] no
llamado [__] [__] y la mayor [__] no
the biggest [ __ ] piece of [ __ ] on the internet and the
la mayor [__] [__] de internet y la
worst kind
peor
chill chill chill eh chill chill
calaña chill chill chill eh chill chill
chill low profile Abi Abi doesn't mess
chill perfil bajito Abi Abi no se mete
with anyone
con nadie
Abi av vi goes quietly eh without wanting to
Abi av vi va tranquilita eh sin querer
go out in
salir en
clip av vi goes quietly
clip av vi va tranquilita
eh I have nothing there will never exist
eh yo no hay nada nunca va a existir
absolutely nothing that I can do the
absolutamente nada que yo pueda hacer yo
most I'm going to do is go as
lo máximo que voy a hacer es ir lo
much as I can my
máximo que pueda mi
chill chill thing now yes G over
rollo de chill de chill ahora sí G over
man let's see no gameover but you can
hombre a ver no gameover pero le puedes
report him Yeah but I'm not going to report him let's
reportar Sí pero yo no le voy a reportar
see how I could I could sue him
a ver como podr la podría estar demandar
for those things he
por esas cosas que ha
said you disconnected with the Tommy thing and
dicho te desconectaste con lo de Tommy y
now here Haha the Tommy thing which
ahora aquí Jaja lo de Tommy que
is the Tommy thing which my brother knows what it
es lo de tomy que mi hermano se lo que
is but obviously I can't be there I don't
es pero evidentemente no puedo estar no
report or anything say whatever you want that's it it's
reporto ni nada que digas lo que quiera
for one day I don't sue let's see the
está es lo por un día no demand a ver el
problem I already put the bar I already put the
problema Yo ya pongo la vara Yo yo ya la
bar is that I don't even put it  that they
vara es que no la pongo ni siquiera en
call me a stalker the worst [ __ ]
que me llamen acosador la peor [__]
[ __ ] on the internet and I let that
[__] de internet y ya eso lo dejo
go if it's one day you know or so That's the that that's
pasar si es un día sabes o sea Esa es la
the level where I already have
ese ese es ya el nivel donde yo tengo ya
the bar currently I already have the level where he
la vara actualmente yo ya el nivel lo
does it very
tengo ya en en el que lo haga muy
frequently where he does it almost
habitualmente en el que lo haga casi
every day you know I mean if he tells me
todos los días sabes o sea si me lo dice
one day well you know there come on I already
un día bueno sabes ahí venga va Yo ya el
have the level where where he
nivel lo tengo en el que en el que me lo
tells me very often for months Oh if you
dice muy a menudo durante meses Ah si me
tell me one day a couple of days a
lo dices un día un par de días una
weeks Relax I won't report you I won't
semanas Tranquila no te reporto no te
do anything to you Javi Look at Abi's chat
hago nada Javi Mira el chat de la Abi
imagine seriously that your father is Javi
imaginan a seri que tu padre sea Javi
Oliveira damn it's true imagine seriously
oliveira [__] es verdad imaginan a
that your father is Javi
seri que tu padre sea Javi
Oliveira what a pain in the ass about Javi Oliveira's son damn Javi is fooling around he
oliveira qué putada lo del hijo de Javi
's disgusting
oliveira [__] Javi tontea es asqueroso
in every sense and he's a
da qusim en todos los sentidos y es un
misogynist Let's see I don't think uncle shur is
misógino A ver no creo que tío shur sea
the same as Javi Oliveira you are good at
lo mismo que Javi oliveira eres buena en
your
tu
job damn he is a little harassed by the
trabajo [__] es un poco acosado por el
chat no I mean literally  these people
chat no O sea literalmente esta gente se
project themselves and are literally what they have
proyectan y son literalmente lo que lo
eh I mean this is literally a
que tienen eh o sea esto es literal un
hate chat literal hate chat dude I mean
odio literal un chat de odio tío o sea
here I'm not going to let you guys say
aquí yo no os dejo a ustedes que pongáis
that Abi is disgusting or what the [ __ ] is that about
que Abi es asquerosa o que qué putada lo
the son of No because she doesn't have a son
de la el hijo de No porque no tiene hijo
no
no
But this is a completely
Pero esto es un chat completamente de
hate chat eh mentioning relatives and everything eh I
odio eh mencionando familiares y todo eh
mean here notice eh they always say
o sea aquí fijaros eh que siempre dicen
no it's like Javi Oliveira and the guy Sur and
no es que Javi oliveira y el tío sur y
the nauter are dedicated to such no
el nauter se dedican a tal no
literally this is a hate chat and
literalmente esto es un chat de odio y
this is a girl who is
esto es una tía que está
defaming This girl surely if you
difamando Esta tía seguramente si a mí
condemn me imagine for insulting
me condenas en imagínate por insultar a
someone in any of the lawsuits that they
alguien en alguna de las demandas que me
file against me I'm sure she would be the typical chick
ponen seguro que sería la pava la típica
that would do the ret to you and say Finally
que los ret te haría y diría Por fin se
justice has been done when she she has
ha hecho justicia cuando ella ella tiene
the same the same type of expressions or
la misma el mismo tipo de expresiones o
worse than
peor que
me in this clim I'll save it for
yo a este clim me lo guardaré para
when she tells me something if she
cuando ella me diga algo si me vuelve a
tells me something again in the past But man
decir algo en el pasado Pero hombre
look at the chat eh the chat and it has
fíjate tú el chat eh el chat y tiene
moderators well wait no no no  no no it's not
moderadores bueno espérate no no no no
that I have moderators It's that this
no es que tenga moderadores Es que este
imagine being born and your father is jav
imagina nacer y que tu padre sea jav
olira is that this is a moderator is a
olira es que este es moderador es
moderator kid
moderador chaval
I was referring to when tomy shouted aibel
me refería a cuando tomy grito aibel
Haha a kiss Thanks a lot dude I mean
Jaja un beso Muchas gracias tío o sea
how the hell are we going to ask the
cómo [__] vamos a pedir que los
moderators to put order in the
moderadores estén poniendo orden en el
chat if its [ __ ] hate chat or
chat si es que su [__] chat de odio o
whatever Of course we could report this
sea Claro que podríamos reportar esto
but I'm not going to do it totally cultural clash
pero no lo voy a hacer choque cultural
with another Spanish woman but
totalmente con otra española pero choque
cultural clash I mean look at you eh How are you going to
cultural o sea fíjate tú eh Cómo vas a
ask the moderators to put
pedir tú que los moderadores pongan
order if she's not supposed to see it or
orden si ella se supone que no lo ve o
whatever the comments are okay if
lo que sea los comentarios vale si es
the [ __ ] moderators are
que los [__] moderadores me están
insulting me
insultando a
the moderators are insulting I mean imagine
mí los moderadores están insultando O
Imagine that I have look
imagínate Imagínate que yo tengo mira
nothing Just content the
nada Solo contenido los carroñeros de
internet scavengers Javi disgusting Javi is
internet Javi asqueroso Javi es
disgusting da Asís imo in every
asquerosísimo da Asís imo en todos los
sense and a mis I mean imagine that I
sentidos y un mis O sea imagínate que yo
have a moderator here who is
tengo aquí un moderador que está
saying Avi is disgusting she's a filthy
diciendo Avi es una asquerosa es una
woman imagine
[__] imagínate
dude
tío
imagine ad Max admax is  what I can
imagínate ad Max admax es lo que puedo
do is do my thing and never talk about
hacer ir a mi rollo Y no hablar nunca de
these topics but obviously there are days when I've been
estos temas Pero obviamente Hay días que
feeling a little
me ha tocado un poquito la la vibra
sensitive to be honest because it's not
sensible la verdad porque no es no es
easy to see how people make up what they
fácil ver como la gente se inventa lo
want from you and other people
que quiere de ti y la otra gente
react as if it were really like that I mean you have
Reacciona como si realmente fuese así O
those situations every
sea tenéis esas situaciones todos los
day Eh it gets to
días Eh es que llega a
be Who's an [ __ ] Look who's an
ser Quién es gilipolla Mira quién es
[ __ ] this is another moderator Who
gilipolla esto es otro moderador Quién
's an [ __ ] will die being another
es gilipolla morirá siendo otro
[ __ ] very mentally draining not
gilipolla muy drenante mentalmente no
only in the sense
solo en el sentido de
that it hurts but in the end if you
que eso duele sino que al final si tú
are minimally weak-minded or you have
eres de mente mínimamente débil o tienes
a slightly weaker day you read it and you
un día un poco más débil tú lo lees y te
believe it you know like what
lo crees sabes en plan lo que dicen
they say it sinks into your head just
ellos se te cala en la cabeza al igual
like anyone
que cualquier
eh what's the word I'm
eh có Cuál es la palabra que estoy
looking for defect Or
buscando defecto O
not when you feel you have a
no cuando sientes que tienes un
defect insecurity eh There are many your
defecto inseguridad eh Hay muchas tu
threshold for offense is so high that you're almost
umbral de ofensa está tan alto que casi
earthquake proof let's see
sos a prueba de terremotos ya ver
Veronica is sad eh It's sad that
Verónica es triste eh Es triste que
we have to say that eh take
tengamos que decir eso eh cogerme
screenshots of her chat yeah  I'm not going to I do
capturas de su chat eso sí no las voy a
n't know if greetings here or one of the
no sé si salud por aquí o alguno de los
Mods please I'm not going to report it eh I'm
los Mods porfa no lo voy a reportar eh
not going to report it but take
No lo voy a reportar pero cogerme
screenshots of the chat of the things you
capturas del chat de las cosas que
're saying please from the moderators
estáis diciendo porfi de los moderadores
especially eh Well and people no
sobre todo eh Bueno y la gente no
disgusting
asqueroso
misogynist your son I don't know what the son of
misógino tu hijo no sé qué el hijo de
Javier Veira take it take all that
Javier veira cogerlo cogerlo todo eso
please It's insecurities that people create in you
porfa Es inseguridades que te crea la
like teenagers they
gente en plan de adolescentes te
insult you something that maybe even when you're
insultan algo que a lo mejor incluso de
older people will like but
mayor le va a gustar a la gente pero
since they've insulted you they've
como a ti te han insultado te lo han
put it in your head and even if it's not
metido en la cabeza y Aunque eso no sea
real the complex and the
real se te crea el complejo y la
insecurity are created and with this Exactly the
inseguridad y con esto Exactamente lo
same if people repeat repeat repeat repeat
mismo si la peña repite repite repite
repeat something you say it's your
repite repite una cosa tú dices es tu
mind you don't say it you report it you
mente no lo dices tú lo tú repórtalo te
No I'm not going to report her I'm not going to
No yo no voy a reportarla no voy a
report her your mind plans start to believe it
reportarla tu mente plan se lo empieza a
start to tell the s who have done
empieza a decir a loj s que ha hecho
this it's like no no no no don't even think about
esto es como no no no no no se os vaya a
reporting
ocurrir reportar
Eh well anyone can commit  a
Eh bueno cualquiera podemos cometer un
mistake Okay, nothing happens but if
error Ya está no pasa nada pero que si
we act like this we won't end up family the
nos ponemos así no acabamos familia el
best just called me cancer I don't know
millor me acaba de llamar cáncer no sé
how many
cuántas
times one thing people who don't know who you are
veces una cosa gente que no sabe quién
because I'm going to tell you one thing is that
eres porque una cosa os voy a decir que
sometimes you forget You're never going to
es que a veces se os olvida jamás Vais a
know who any [ __ ] streamer or
saber quién es ningún [__] streamer ni
youtuber or profile that you see on the internet is, you
youtuber ni perfil que veáis en internet
don't know anyone, anyone, anyone, or you're
no conocéis a nadie a nadie a nadie ni
never going to do it, not because you see a person on a
jamás no por ver a una persona en una
screen do you know who they are, you know what they're like, you haven't
pantalla sabes quién es sabes cómo es no
seen how they talk to their parents, you haven't
has visto cómo le habla a los padres no
seen what their childhood was like, you haven't seen
has visto qué infancia ha tenido no has
what complexes they have, you have
visto qué complejos tiene no has visto
n't seen how they take care of their friends when they're drunk, you haven't seen how they just wake up, you have
no has visto cómo está recién despertada
n't seen how they talk when they're sad, you haven't seen how they are with their
triste no has visto cómo es con su
partner when they're alone, you haven't seen
pareja cuando están a solas no has visto
anything, you don't know who anyone is and people
nada no sabes quién es nadie y la gente
on the internet pretend they know
en internet se la da de que conoce a
everyone and because of them they make up a
todo el mundo y por ellos se inventan un
profile to then criticize them and it's
perfil para luego criticarlo y es una
crazy, it's [ __ ]
locura es una [__]
crazy, seriously, it's [ __ ] crazy And
locura en serio es una [__] locura Y de
you really end up going crazy but
verdad que te acabas volviendo loca pero
thanks to what happened to me last year
gracias a lo que me pasó el año pasado
I  I've worked hard to have my life
yo he trabajado mucho en tener mi vida
my life outside of the internet of hanging out
mi vida fuera de internet de quedar
with my friends a lot of going out for
mucho con mis amigos de ir a tomar
beers talking to them playing
cervezas de hablar con ellos de jugar
off stream without looking at such as having everything
off Stream sin mirar tal de tener todo
muted of of trying to go to the gym of
muteado de de de intentar al gimnasio de
reforming my eating schedule better I
reformarme el horario de comer mejor o
mean because when it comes down to it
sea porque a la que de verdad
your mental state depends on four
tu estado mental depende de cuatro
guys who can say
brados que pueden llegar a decir
awful things without any problem
barbaridades sin ningún tipo de problema
about it
al
you're going to commit suicide it works like
respecto te vas a suicidar funciona en
joano Thank you very much welcome I
plan joano Muchas gracias bienvenido o
mean I don't even know How many insults or
sea yo no sé ni Cuántos insultos ni
How many awful things have been said here
Cuántas barbaridades ha dicho aquí
eh be level
eh sea
level losers the biggest [ __ ] inter the
nivel pringos la mayores Mier inter la
biggest garbage harassers and ends up saying it's
mayor basura acosadores y acaba diciendo
not that if you pay attention to the things
no es que si le echas cuenta las cosas
these people say to you you're
que te dicen esta gente te vas a
going to commit suicide [ __ ] we haven't told you any so you go commit suicide girl And you enter that game you commit suicide So this doesn't mean that having a bad day and touching my dick one day eh It affects me in
toque la [__] un día eh Me afecte en
any way because it doesn't affect me I mean I'm
nada porque no me afecta o sea estoy
happy with what I have I'm super
contenta con lo que tengo soy super
privileged I'm super
privilegiada estoy super
proud and to think that despite it I'm going to
orgullosa y pensa que le pese voy a
continue  talking about whatever my
seguir hablando de lo que me salgan los
balls come out And if one day I have to
[__] Y si algún día tengo que volver
defend someone again I'm going to do it and if
a defender a alguien lo voy a hacer y si
one day I have to get into a
algún día tengo que volver a meterme una
ruckus again I'm going to do it or so let's
movida lo voy a hacer o sea eso
wait we're going to do it Surely sure if you
esperados lo vamos Seguro seguro si tú
think that eh 4 10 34 fairies are going to
te crees que eh 4 10 34 fadas van a
make me stop using my voice and
hacer que yo deje de utilizar mi voz y
my space to fight for what I believe in and
mi espacio para luchar por lo que creo y
what I see you smoke joints another thing is that I'm
lo que veo fumas porros otra cosa es que
doing it again in ways that I've
lo vuelvo a hacer de maneras que he
done in the past that there are many things
hecho en el pasado que hay muchas cosas
that I for not having done them right
de las que me por no haberlas hecho bien
because there are things Uncle Shura has
porque hay cosas el tío shura ha
responded to
respondido de
this Uncle Shura responded this was not
esto respondió el tío shura esto no lo
on the news That's it, it's
puso en el noticiero Ya está
not 3:10 anymore, man I have to,
no son ya las 3-10 tío me tengo que
okay, come on, one more and I'm leaving, one
bueno venga una una más y me voy una
more thing and I'm leaving okay because it was
cosa más y me voy vale porque es que fue
strong man, I just saw the thumbnail,
fuertecito tío vi la miniatura nada más
eh, I just saw the thumbnail, man,
eh vi la miniatura nada más tío
lol it's that I don't even know what, I don't even know what
eh lol es que no sé ni qué no sé ni qué
I'm going to put on this extract, the
le voy a poner yo a este ex tracto la
truth is because the thumbnail is strong
verdad porque la la miniatura es fuerte
eh [ __ ] the thumbnail is strong everyone  they
eh [__] la miniatura es fuerte todos
hate iton Gameplay and he puts the
odian a iton Gameplay y pone a lo
first thing he puts me in the thumbnail
primero que me pone a mí en la miniatura
twice I don't know why it's worth the first thing he
dos veces no sé por qué vale lo primero
puts me in the thumbnail
que me pone a mí en la miniatura dos
twice I don't know why
veces no sé por qué
and and
y
and it says there kidnapping a
y y pone ahí secuestrando una niña
little girl Town Gameplays the famous
pequeña Town Gameplays el famoso
youtuber accused of horrible crimes
youtuber acusado de crímenes horribles
returned to the networks Will he finally
regresó a las redes Será que por fin
respond to his funa now we will see him
respondió a su funa ahora lo veremos
welcome gentlemen and the almost
bienvenido caballeros y las casi
nonexistent ladies who see this there are
inexistentes damas que vean esto hay
many youtubers who went from being
muchos youtubers que pasaron de ser
loved to being hated by everyone and
amados a ser odiados por todo el mundo y
one of the best examples of this is
uno de los mejores ejemplos de esto es
itown Gameplays who a few years ago was
itown Gameplays quien hace unos años Fue
accused of being a gromer and from time to
acusado de ser un gromer y cada cierto
time his controversy revives and they
tiempo su polémica revive y le vuelven a
throw hate at him again below I will tell you if there
tirar hate a continuación les contaré si
is new information about it
acaso hay nueva información al respecto
if they tried him if he spoke out on
si le hicieron el juicio si se pronunció
the subject and we will see how he is
respecto al tema y veremos Cómo se
currently Álvaro Martínez or itown
actualidad Álvaro Martínez o itown
Gameplays is a Spanish youtuber with more
Gameplays es un youtuber español con más
than 15 million subscribers who
de 15 millones de suscriptores que
began his career in 2011 opening a
empezó su carrera en el 2011 abriendo un
channel called HM Álvaro where
canal llamado HM Álvaro en donde
he uploaded pine they have not funado  for the
subió pino no le han funado por las
thumbnails I don't know but the truth is
miniaturas No lo sé pero la verdad es
that this thumbnail seems very
que esta miniatura Me parece muy
delicate to me man it seems very with how
delicada tío me parece muy con lo
silly I
tontito que yo
had I don't know
tuve no lo sé
everyone hates Win michu everyone hates
todos odian a Win michu todos odian a
Comanche everyone hates Jer mo everyone
Comanche todos odian a Jer mo todos
hates Agustín I mean it's a series I
odian a Agustín o sea es una serie
understand it's
entiendo
not a series I understand no yes it is a
no es una serie entiendo no sí es una
series all the videos are called the
serie se llaman todos los vídeos
same all the videos are called the
iguales se llaman todos los videos
same several songs that I don't know about
iguales varias canciones que no sé
you but those thumbnails scare me
ustedes pero a mí esas miniaturas me dan
a lot but well since I get
mucho [__] miedo pero bueno como consigo
very few visits at the time with that
muy pocas visitas en su momento con ese
channel the following year he decided to create a
canal decidió al año siguiente crearse
new one where Yes, he was able to grow
uno nuevo donde Sí fue capaz de crecer
quickly and become very popular all
rápidamente y volverse muy popular todo
thanks to the fact that he focused his content on a I
gracias a que enfocó Su contenido a un
want to see
Quiero ver
eh Why did he put the thumbnail for us
eh Por qué nos ha puesto la miniatura
okay now we don't know all this
vale ya todo esto no lo conocemos
we know everything that
conocemos todo lo que mostró
Dallas showed well we know that this one
Dallas bueno conocemos que este le
defended him it's true you it's true you this
defendió es verdad tú es verdad tú este
the 40 year old stutterer defended him
el tartaja de 40 años le defendió
visits this as it does not include Town
visitas esto como no incluye a Town
Gameplays whose channel was revived for the second
Gameplays cuyo canal revivió por segunda
time thanks to this game and well at one
vez gracias a este juego y bueno en un
point they started talking about
momento dado comenzaron a hablar sobre
him and one of the Dead's friends asked
él y uno de los amigos del Dead preguntó
if he is really still active  on YouTube
si en serio sigue activo en YouTube a
despite the funa to which Al Capone
pesar de la funa a lo que Al Capone
responded yes because anyway
respondió que sí porque de todos modos
the accusations were false and that he
las acusaciones eran falsas y que él
only talks to adult women you're
solo habla con mujeres adultas estás
saying that there is a Gameplay that sucks
diciendo que está un Gameplay chupa
content but it's that apart from the yes I have
contenido pero es que aparte el sí he
been generous [ __ ] I told him 40 years
sido generoso cabron le he dicho 40 años
that the guy lied or rather the Al Capone thing It
que el tío mintió o sea lo del alcapones
was on a Dead steam it was invented for
Fue en un steam del Dead se inventó por
the [ __ ] face that the Lighton thing had been
la [__] cara que lo de lighton se había
publicly denied no no but yes
desmentido públicamente no no pero si
that subject was super denied it was proven
ese tema quedó super desmentido se probó
that it was false he made it up for the [ __ ]
que era falso se lo inventó por la [__]
face to
cara para
defend him for the face he made it up or
defenderlo por la cara se lo inventó o
rather like 30 videos of the two in
sea como 30 videos del dos en
D
D videos
FES videos of the
FES de la
funada f was false the funada was false
funada f fue falsa la funada fue falsa
the
la
funada didn't see Uy they don't know the
funada no vieron Uy no se saben el
gossip no no they didn't see Uy they don't know the
chisme no no no vieron Uy no se saben el
gossip don't be he made it up dude to
chisme no sea se lo inventa tío para
defend his friend What happened what
defender al amigo Qué pasó qué
happened Well nothing they caught the girl
pasó Pues nada que cacharon a la chava
who was pure nonsense everything they caught the
que era puro pedo todo que cacharon a la
girl who was pure nonsense everything he
chava que era puro pedo todo se lo
made it up to defend his friend
inventó para defender al amigo
kid  he made it up but to the face they
chaval se lo inventó pero by the face
totally caught the girl that it
totalmente que cacharon a la chava que
was pure nonsense all the what what which
era puro pedo todo el qué qué cuál
when it was pure story the
cuándo era puro cuento la
dick didn't see And on top of that and on top of that the embarrassment
[__] no vieron Y encima y encima el
What are you doing dude I mean aren't you
papelón Qué hace tío O sea no te da
ashamed dude you're a father dude the
vergüenza tío que eres padre tío el
role he plays No they didn't find out about the
papel que hace No no se enteraron del
gossip they didn't find out about the gossip Oh no don't
chisme no se enteraron del chisme Ay no
tell me
no me digas
then he's not a pedophile dude he's not a
entonces no es un pedofil pipín no es un
dick let loose Yeah but he's not a
verg suelta Sí pero no es un
pedophile then he explains that all the
pedofil luego explica que todas las
things over 18 that he wrote and the video
cosas más 18 que ta escribió y el video
of his Tula were directed to
de su Tula eran dirigidas a mayores de
adults but not girls and that the girls
edad pero no a niñas y que las chicas
who wrote the thread are
que escribieron el hilo son unas
liars who wanted to destroy his
mentirosas que quisieron destruir su
career and since they didn't file a
carrera y como no presentaron la
complaint Then we shouldn't
denuncia Entonces no hay que
believe them even more it became milky
creerles aú más quedó como lechoso
now I mean photo where he appears grabbing
ya o sea foto donde sale agarrándose acá
the voli here
el voli
according to me it is true I mean that's where
el según yo sí es cierta o sea hasta ahí
things ended but it wasn't a minor or anything no no no no
cosa pero no fue ni una menor ni nada no
What's the matter damn Raza What's the matter and the
no Qué pedo [__] Raza Qué pedo y el
Town has never sued Dallas has
Town no ha demandado al Dallas nunca
never reported
nunca ha denunciado al
Dallas or  be the gey yes he sent photos but they
Dallas o sea el gey sí mandó fotos pero
weren't to
no eran a
minors aj ah But then who did he
menores aj ah Pero entonces a quién se
send them to if those girls in the video are the ones you
las mandó si esas chicas del vídeo son
know if those girls are the ones
las que sabes si esas chicas son las que
who posted it that they were other
las que lo pusieron que fueron otras
girls who gave the information to
chicas que le dieron la información a
other girls so that they could tell it,
otras niñas para que lo contaran ellas
take out gossip channels and so on gy to
sacá canales de chismes y así gy para
start with no
empezar no
siren and well here channels it's that [ __ ]
siren y pues acá canales es que [__]
trying to find out and they give their
tratando de averiguar y dan su opinión
stupid opinion without knowing, I mean [ __ ]
pendeja sin saber o sea pinches Morros
18 year old kids who don't know anything about laws
de 18 años que no saben nada ni de leyes
or anything
ni ni de ninguna
[ __ ] I mean it's nothing more Ah well
chingada O sea que nada más es Ah pues
I think so true because well
pues yo creo que sí verdad porque pues
the screenshot looks nothing [ __ ] your
el screenshot se ve nada [__] a tu
mother I mean if you go to yes they're going to blame
madre o sea si vas a si van a culpar a
someone watch out I'm not defending anything I
alguien ojo No estoy defendiendo nada No
'm not defending anything it says invent
estoy defendiendo nada dice invent
you have to have a [ __ ] complaint in
tienes que tener una [__] denuncia en la
hand Ah if not that person is still
mano Ah si no esa persona sigue siendo
innocent gy there's no more you have to
inocente gy no hay más tienes que
find something to
encontrar con qué
[ __ ] with and well here gossip channels and
chingar y pues acá canales de chismes y
so on gey to start with
así gey para empezar no sirven para nada
gossip channels are useless n
los canales de chismes n no sirve para
the fact that he only insulted is useless  to
nada el hecho de que solo insultara a
those who were against him he did not
los que estaban en su contra no
convince anyone that he was right
convenció a nadie de que tenía la razón
and they insulted him on Twitter for defending
y lo insultaron en Twitter por defender
an alleged pedophile In addition to
a un supuesto pedófilo Además de que
attacking the gossip youtubers when he
atacó los youtubers de chismes cuando él
is the one who spread information without
es el que esparció información sin
backing it up with evidence and reviving a
respaldarla con pruebas y revivir una
controversy No no it is that he
polé No no es que él se lo inventó
literally made it up he made it up because of his face, I mean it is
literalmente se lo inventó por la cara o
not to say Well then I believe
sea no es decir Bueno pues yo me creo a
Town no no no no no no he made it up that
Town no no no no no no se inventó que la
in the Dead's live
en el directo del Dead
Taking advantage of the fact that it will have an audience I
Aprovechando que el de tendrá audiencia
don't know how much audience it has he made it up
no sé cuánta audiencia tiene se inventó
Ah you did not find out about the gossip they
Ah no te enteraste del chisme la
caught the girl who was lying
cacharon a la chica que estaba mintiendo
and it's like When where did that happen I did not
y es como Cuándo dónde pasó eso yo no me
find out [ __ ] look we have discussed that subject
enteré [__] mira que ese tema lo hemos
but
tratado pero
where where did that happen that they caught her
dónde dónde pasó eso que la trincar
lying I want to see them [ __ ] [ __ ] I am
mintiendo los quiero ver [__] [__] me
interested in knowing that episode does not exist it is not
me interesa saber ese episodio no existe
anywhere old mica that has not been
parte mica antigua de la que ya no se
talked about for more than 2 years I find it
hablaba hace más de 2 años me parece
curious that she blamed others
curioso que le echara la culpa a otros
for reviving the funa or taking advantage of
de revivir la funa o aprovecharse de la
it when she did Exactly  not to
misma cuando hizo Exactamente eso sin
mention that it makes no sense to complain
mencionar que no tiene sentido quejarse
about gossip channels talking about
de que los canales de salseo hablen de
controversies because that's their [ __ ]
las controversias porque es su [__]
job but oh well The fact is that
trabajo pero bueno El caso es que
millions of people kept fighting
millones de personas siguieron peleando
to see who was right Until
para ver quién tenía razón Hasta que
eventually they got tired And again They
eventualmente se cansaron Y de nuevo Se
forgot about the subject however
olvidaron del tema sin embargo la funa
tawn's funa was not completely forgotten and
de tawn no fue olvidada por completo y
just a year later it came back to life
tan solo un año después volvió a revivir
Yes yes for the third time for some reason
Sí sí por tercera vez por algún motivo
people do not get tired of arguing about
la gente no se cansa de discutir sobre
an old controversy about which there is no
una controversia vieja de la que no hay
new news it's incredible there will not
noticias nuevas es increíble no va a
be any news it seemed that the
haber ninguna noticia parecía que el
subject was forgotten but last year there was
tema fue olvidado pero el año pasado se
a new news about tawn And the thing is
via es una nueva noticia sobre tawn Y es
that in September he had a son who he
que en septiembre tuvo un hijo al que le
named no something he announced through
puso no algo que anunció mediante
Instagram many congratulated him for being a
Instagram muchos lo felicitaron por ser
father and wished him good luck but there
padre y le desearon buena suerte pero
were also people who continued to remember
también hubo gente que seguía recordando
his old funa and insulted him calling him a
su vieja funa y lo insultaron llamándolo
pedophile and a groomer some went so
pedófilo y groomer algunos llegaron al
far as to make some very
extremo de hacer unos chistes muy
shady jokes Like for example when his
turbios Como por ejemplo que cuando su
boyfriend grows up and Us internet will find out
chico crezca y Us internet se enterará
about the controversy his
de la polémica en la que se metió su
father got into and he will be traumatized for life
padre y quedará traumado de por vida
after  watch the video Well you know
tras ver el video de Bueno ya saben
others went much further to the point
otros llegaron mucho más lejos al punto
of saying that he abused a 15
de decir que abusó de una chica de 15
year old girl and got her pregnant to have his child
años y la embarazó para tener a su hijo
a joke that was repeated ad
un chiste que fue repetido hasta el
nauseam and literally couldn't get into
cansancio y literalmente no podía entrar
a p of his about his daughter without 20
a un p suyo sobre su hija sin que 20
random people repeating it believing themselves to be
Random lo repitieran creyendose
original another type of joke that
originales otro tipo de chiste que
esparon const incredible how good
esparon const increíble lo de bueno que
I painted in the thumbnail because this
pintaba yo en la miniatura porque este
guy put me in the thumbnail
tío me ha puesto en la miniatura
pipepino because you put me there in the
pipepino porque me has puesto aí en la
thumbnail Ah because he messes with the
miniatura Ah porque se mete con los
channels of se or no how
canales de se o no
tremendous what about the alcapones I didn't
e tremendo lo del alcapones no me
remember eh tremendous what about the alcapone
acordaba eh tremendísimo lo del alcapone
man I mean how he invented it all over his
tío o sea cómo se inventó por toda la
face it's to defend his uncle friend from
cara es para defender a su amigo tío de
something so so ugly because I would [ __ ] and it's like don't you do
algo tan tan feo porque yo cogería y es
n't hang out with
como no te no te juntes
more people around here we leave the live I'm
más gente por aquí dejamos el directito
going to sleep eh see you see you
me voy a dormir eh nos vemos nos vemos
tomorrow most likely Ah tomorrow tomorrow
mañana muy probablemente Ah mañana
tomorrow I start my full
mañana mañana empiezo mi clase de full
Body class tomorrow I start my full
Body mañana empiezo mi clase de full
Body class do you think I'll last from here until
Body creéis que duraré de aquí a
summer do you think that  I'll get here by
verano creéis que llegaré de aquí a
summer doing full
verano haciendo full
Body no way guys this is the
Body no que sí chavales que esta es la
good one this summer is the good one this
buena este verano es el bueno este
summer is the definitive one what was said let's see it
verano es el definitivo lo dicho a ver
in parts before I go I remind you
por partes antes de irme os lo recuerdo
Okay now that there are more people I
Vale ahora que hay más gente os lo
remind you before I
recuerdo antes de
go I open a thread denying with evidence
irme abro hilo desmintiendo con pruebas
the girl who accuses with manche let's see
a la chica que acusa con manche a ver
but there is a
pero hay
penis there is a penis
pene hay pene
man
tío
Well but it's censored I understand that's
Bueno pero está censurados entiendo que
not a problem
eso no pasa
okay come on I'm going to try I'm going to
nada vale venga voy a intentar voy a
[Music]
[Música]
try I'm going to try to see it
intentar voy a intentar verlo
without anything I see it on Twitter man I see it
sin nada lo veo yo en Twitter tío lo veo
on Twitter I see it on Twitter Tomorrow I'll
yo en Twitter lo veo en Twitter Mañana
put it on the news and that's it no
lo pongo en el noticiero y ya está no
what was I going to tell you what's with
que os iba a decir que es lo de lo del
Instagram please what's with
Instagram porfa lo del
tiktok what's with tiktok please man I mean the
tiktok lo del tiktok porfa tío O sea la
thing is that well they've closed the
movida es que bueno nos han cerrado el
tior and I need us all to do the
tior y necesito que hagamos todos lo
same thing we did
mismo que hicimos
uh the time we got it back okay in case
eh la vez que lo recuperamos vale por si
someone doesn't know it's not the first
alguien no lo sabe ya no es la primera
time they've closed my Tito I understand that they
vez que me cierran el Tito entiendo que
will be some stalker or some of these
serán algún acosador o alguno de esta
usual people not reporting in bulk or that they have
gente de siempre no reportando a saco o
found  the trick is not to
que han encontrado el truco no de que
write in the reports or whatever
escribir en los reportes o lo que sea
okay the move is very easy okay I
vale la movida es muy fácil vale
need all of you who are here
Necesito que todos los que estáis aquí
absolutely all of you who are here
absolutamente todos los que estáis aquí
please okay you have to take you go to
porfa vale tenéis que [__] os vais a
your tiktok profile okay to
vuestro perfil de tiktok vale para
help me you go to your
ayudarme os vais a vuestro perfil de
tiktok profile if you do it several times each one I do
tikt si lo hacéis varias veces cada uno
n't care either okay you click here on
tampoco me importa vale le dais aquí a
the three
las tres
lines settings and
rayitas ajustes y
privacy report a
privacidad informar de un
problem
problema
send a
enviar una
report send a
denuncia enviar una
report and I wrote the account called
denuncia y escribí la cuenta llamada
@abi oliveira 5 has been banned by
@abi oliveira 5 ha sido baneada por
mistake Please restore as soon as possible
error Por favor restaura cuanto antes
I am your follower or whatever okay but
soy su seguidor o lo que sea vale pero
please restore the account I don't know
por favor restauradle la cuenta no sé
what okay And if you put a screenshot it would be
qué vale Y si ponéis una captura sería
ideal okay put a
ideal vale ponéis una captura de
screenshot eh you can find it
pantalla eh que la encontráis
quickly if you put
rápidamente si ponéis
tiktok javio oliveira 5 in
tiktok javio oliveira 5 en
Google it will appear okay look
Google os va a aparecer vale mira
here man
aquí tío es
we are on the verge of 100,000
que estamos a las puertas de los 100000
man we are not going to get there in life man with
tío no vamos a llegar en la vida tío con
these people who don't leave us alone
esta gente que no nos dejan en paz
man
tío
okay for example this screenshot you can
vale por ejemplo esta captura podéis
put if you have an account a screenshot
poner si tenéis una cuenta una captura
of the  better tell but if you don't pass
de la cuenta mejor pero si no paséis
This is
Esto
okay I've said it okay do it and well
vale lo he dicho vale hacerlo y pues
nothing would be Cool if you went to the
nada estaría Guay que fuerais para el
video on the main Channel take a
vídeo del Canal principal le echara un
look at it okay I'm going to bed because I have to get
vistazo vale Yo me voy a la cama que me
up man in no time man in
tengo que levantar tío en nada tío en
no time
nada
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
eh in 67 hours let's
eh en 67 horita
see probably on Mondays and
a ver seguramente los lunes y los
Wednesdays what I will do will probably
miércoles lo que haré seguramente
be either not do it live or
será o no hacer directo o hacer
only do one of the
solamente uno de los
two on the main video yeah I'll even
dos al vídeo del principal sí Hasta los
see you two times okay Come on then go
veo dos veces vale Venga pues venga iros
to the video on the main Channel and
para el vídeo del Canal principal y
give it a like and give it something okay guys
darle like y darle cosita vale guapos
see you tomorrow the day after a big hug
nos vemos mañana pasado un abrazote
Well tomorrow there is a video on the
Bueno mañana hay vídeo en el canal
main channel eh see you guys
principal eh nos vemos chicos
bye
chao